non_propaganda
What O
allegations O
does O
the O
letter O
make O
? O

propaganda
In O
the B-DATE
last I-DATE
20 I-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
“ O
conservative O
” O
Catholics B-NORP
have O
pointed O
to O
the O
flourishing O
– O
mainly O
in O
the O
US B-GPE
– O
of O
some O
groups O
of O
sisters O
who O
had O
turned O
away O
from O
the O
“ O
intense O
and O
fruitful O
path O
” O
and O
re O
- O
established O
some O
of O
the O
traditional O
accoutrements O
of O
the O
religious O
life O
. O

non_propaganda
In O
fact O
, O
both O
Giuliani B-PERSON
and O
Bolton B-PERSON
have O
been O
on O
the O
payroll O
of O
the O
MeK B-PERSON
and O
have O
received O
tens B-MONEY
of I-MONEY
thousands I-MONEY
of I-MONEY
dollars I-MONEY
to O
speak O
to O
their O
followers O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
Vatican B-ORG
has O
said O
it O
“ O
worked O
with O
almost B-CARDINAL
200 I-CARDINAL
dioceses O
and O
religious O
communities O
worldwide O
to O
raise O
awareness O
and O
to O
educate O
people O
on O
the O
need O
for O
safeguarding O
in O
our O
homes O
, O
parishes O
, O
schools O
, O
hospitals O
, O
and O
other O
institutions O
. O
” O

non_propaganda
There O
are O
those O
who O
say O
, O
“ O
It O
was O
their O
money O
. O

non_propaganda
This O
would O
explain O
why O
he O
will O
not O
a O
“ O
say O
a O
word O
about O
” O
Viganò B-GPE
’ O
s O
charges O
against O
him O
. O

non_propaganda
We O
will O
get O
back O
to O
you O
shortly O
with O
a O
more O
extensive O
response O
. O
” O

propaganda
I O
categorically O
and O
unequivocally O
deny O
the O
allegation O
against O
me O
by O
Dr. O
Ford B-PERSON
. O

propaganda
This O
was O
the O
obstruction O
tactic O
of O
choice O
of O
the O
left O
for O
trying O
to O
secure O
the O
Court B-ORG
seat O
before O
they O
fastened O
on O
to O
this O
latest O
smear O
. O

propaganda
We O
are O
simply O
asked O
to O
take O
the O
pope O
’ O
s O
word O
for O
it O
, O
but O
given O
that O
it O
follows O
his O
astoundingly O
brazen O
lie O
that O
there O
was O
no O
evidence O
for O
Ricca B-ORG
’ O
s O
homosexual O
activity O
in O
the O
first B-ORDINAL
place O
, O
we O
can O
take O
the O
assurance O
for O
what O
it O
seems O
to O
be O
worth O
. O

non_propaganda
In O
May B-DATE
: O

propaganda
The O
judge O
’ O
s O
husband O
is O
a O
figure O
deep O
within O
the O
national O
security O
establishment O
in O
Britain B-GPE
who O
was O
named O
in O
WikiLeaks B-GPE
documents O
. O

non_propaganda
solemnly O
professed O
: O
119 B-CARDINAL

non_propaganda
It O
is O
time O
to O
admit O
that O
there O
is O
a O
homosexual O
subculture O
within O
the O
hierarchy O
of O
the B-ORG
Catholic I-ORG
Church I-ORG
that O
is O
wreaking O
great O
devastation O
in O
the O
vineyard O
of O
the O
Lord O
. O

propaganda
Given O
that O
this O
was O
2009 B-DATE
, O
it O
is O
clear O
that O
the O
plans O
to O
force O
all O
contemplative O
monasteries O
in O
the O
world O
into O
this O
disastrous O
European B-NORP
mould O
were O
well O
under O
way O
long O
before O
Pope O
Benedict B-PERSON
was O
even O
considering O
resigning O
. O

propaganda
Don O
’ O
t O
allow O
yourself O
to O
be O
deceived O
by O
the O
likes O
of O
Jihad O
Al- O
‘ O
Ayesh B-WORK_OF_ART
. O

non_propaganda
“ O
When O
the O
president O
issues O
such O
an O
order O
, O
it O
triggers O
a O
declassification O
review O
process O
that O
is O
conducted O
by O
various O
agencies O
within O
the O
intelligence O
community O
, O
in O
conjunction O
with O
the O
White B-ORG
House I-ORG
counsel O
, O
to O
seek O
to O
ensure O
the O
safety O
of O
America B-GPE
’ O
s O
national O
security O
interests O
, O
” O
a O
Justice B-ORG
Department I-ORG
spokesman O
said O
in O
a O
statement O
. O

non_propaganda
In O
this O
context O
, O
the O
German B-NORP
cardinal O
also O
criticized O
Martin B-PERSON
Luther I-PERSON
's I-PERSON
own O
denial O
of O
man O
's O
free O
will O
and O
his O
teaching O
about O
the O
total O
depravity O
of O
man O
that O
separates O
morality O
from O
the O
relationship O
with O
God O
. O

non_propaganda
Support O
our O
journalism O
Please O
consider O
subscribing O
today B-DATE
to O
support O
stories O
like O
this O
one O
. O

propaganda
` O
` B-WORK_OF_ART
The I-WORK_OF_ART
DNA I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
our I-WORK_OF_ART
culture I-WORK_OF_ART
is I-WORK_OF_ART
preserved I-WORK_OF_ART
. I-WORK_OF_ART

non_propaganda
Former O
head O
of O
the B-ORG
Democratic I-ORG
National I-ORG
Committee I-ORG
, O
Debbie B-PERSON
Wasserman I-PERSON
Schultz I-PERSON
is O
on O
the O
front O
line O
of O
aiding O
and O
abetting O
Awan B-ORG
and O
his O
associates O
as O
has O
been O
revealed O
by O
Luke B-PERSON
Rosiak I-PERSON
of O
The B-ORG
Daily I-ORG
Caller I-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
Last B-DATE
Thursday I-DATE
, O
however O
, O
was O
not O
the O
first B-ORDINAL
time O
Francis B-PERSON
, O
confronted O
unexpectedly O
in O
public O
over O
the O
Barros B-ORG
question O
, O
has O
responded O
testily O
and O
with O
insults O
. O

non_propaganda
And O
Amsterdam B-GPE
. O

non_propaganda
Average O
age O
: O
between B-CARDINAL
64 I-CARDINAL

propaganda
I O
worked O
for O
the O
Guardian B-ORG
for O
a B-DATE
number I-DATE
of I-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
and O
know O
well O
the O
layers O
of O
checks O
that O
any O
highly O
sensitive O
story O
has O
to O
go O
through O
before O
publication O
. O

non_propaganda
From O
the B-FAC
Vatican I-FAC
Palace I-FAC
, O
on O
the B-DATE
day I-DATE
of I-DATE
June I-DATE
5 I-DATE
in I-DATE
the I-DATE
year I-DATE
2017 I-DATE

propaganda
Those O
who O
love O
our O
Holy B-ORG
Mother I-ORG
– O
those O
who O
want O
to O
protect O
her O
boys O
and O
men O
from O
all O
the O
McCarricks O
and O
their O
perverse O
appetites O
– O
mustn O
’ O
t O
be O
deceived O
into O
thinking O
this O
is O
a O
small O
or O
an O
isolated O
issue O
. O

non_propaganda
Defense O
Attorney O
: O
What O
are O
the O
names O
of O
the O
other O
boys O
and O
the O
girl O
who O
were O
present O
? O

propaganda
Let O
the O
thing O
die O
of O
its O
own O
excesses O
, O
for O
as O
the O
“ O
little O
synod O
” O
[ O
the O
2002 B-DATE
“ O
pedophile O
summit O
” O
] O
demonstrates O
, O
the O
men O
who O
control O
this O
establishment O
will O
never O
restore O
it O
to O
anything O
resembling O
the B-ORG
vibrant I-ORG
Church I-ORG
that O
a O
long O
line O
of O
militant O
, O
uncompromising O
Popes B-ORG
delivered O
into O
their O
hands O
at O
Vatican B-ORG
II I-ORG
. O

propaganda
The O
handover O
was O
done O
with O
much O
fanfare O
, O
then O
the O
US B-GPE
, O
France B-GPE
and O
Britain B-GPE
attacked O
Libya B-GPE
and O
overthrew O
Kadaffi B-PERSON
. O

propaganda
Many O
neighbours O
, O
woken O
by O
the O
old O
woman O
’ O
s O
screams O
or O
the O
assaulter O
’ O
s O
religious O
chanting O
, O
called O
the O
police O
Some O
gave O
details O
about O
the O
exact O
location O
of O
the O
assault O
, O
the O
attacker O
’ O
s O
identity O
, O
the O
fact O
he O
vilified O
his O
victim O
as O
a O
Jewish B-NORP
person O
and O
as O
“ O
a O
Satan O
” O
while O
hitting O
her O
, O
or O
even O
— O
as O
far O
as O
the O
Muslim B-NORP
neighbours O
were O
concerned O
— O
the O
Koranic B-PERSON
portions O
he O
chanted O
. O

non_propaganda
We O
’ O
ll O
see O
soon O
enough O
if O
Goldstein B-PRODUCT
’ I-PRODUCT
s I-PRODUCT
prediction O
comes O
true O
. O

non_propaganda
What O
of O
King O
David B-PERSON
? O

propaganda
The O
deeper O
problem O
lies O
in O
homosexual O
networks O
within O
the O
clergy O
which O
must O
be O
eradicated O
. O
” O
These O
homosexual O
networks O
, O
which O
are O
now O
widespread O
in O
many O
dioceses O
, O
seminaries O
, O
religious O
orders O
, O
etc O
. O
, O
act O
under O
the O
concealment O
of O
secrecy O
and O
lies O
with O
the O
power O
of O
octopus O
tentacles O
, O
and O
strangle O
innocent O
victims O
and O
priestly O
vocations O
, O
and O
are O
strangling O
the O
entire O
Church B-ORG
. O

propaganda
We O
’ O
re O
dealing O
with O
probably O
between B-CARDINAL
1,200 I-CARDINAL
and I-CARDINAL
1,400 I-CARDINAL
calls O
and O
emails O
per O
month O
, O
and O
prior O
to O
that O
it O
was O
600 B-CARDINAL
to O
700 B-CARDINAL
. O
” O
But O
according O
to O
Natural B-ORG
News I-ORG
, O
it O
isn O
’ O
t O
just O
the O
rampant O
violence O
worrying O
some O
parents O
. O

non_propaganda
What O
did O
the O
first O
commission O
achieve O
? O

propaganda
Aiken O
was O
unqualified O
for O
her O
role O
, O
except O
in O
the O
ways O
that O
mattered O
to O
the O
Clintons B-PERSON
and O
their O
Dem B-NORP
allies O
. O

propaganda
That O
’ O
s O
what O
the O
mainstream O
media O
, O
forever O
wedded O
to O
the O
official O
story O
no O
matter O
how O
ridiculous O
and O
illogical O
it O
is O
, O
simply O
can O
not O
bring O
themselves O
to O
confront O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
ammunition O
, O
he O
said O
, O
was O
: O

non_propaganda
Nothing O
in O
a O
system O
like O
that O
is O
a O
greater O
threat O
to O
the O
corrupt O
than O
men O
who O
are O
not O
corrupt O
. O

non_propaganda
It O
just O
shows O
what O
sort O
of O
a O
two B-CARDINAL
- O
tier O
system O
we O
have O
here O
. O
'' O

non_propaganda
Total O
employment O
: O
up O
105,000 B-CARDINAL
( O
+0.08 O
percent O
) O

non_propaganda
In O
fact O
, O
this O
binding O
and O
constant O
teaching O
of O
the O
Church B-ORG
was O
reaffirmed O
most O
recently O
in O
her O
most O
authoritative O
modern O
catechism O
, O
which O
holds O
the O
exact O
opposite O
position O
from O
that O
apparently O
held O
by O
many O
bishops O
: O

non_propaganda
With O
What O
the O
Qur B-PERSON
’ O
an O
Meant O
: O
And O
Why O
It O
Matters O
, O
religion O
author O
Garry B-PERSON
Wills I-PERSON
is O
here O
to O
reassure O
us O
: O

non_propaganda
No O
one O
pays O
me O
to O
write O
these O
blog O
posts O
. O

non_propaganda
He O
'd O
stick O
out O
his O
and O
kiss O
us O
with O
his O
tongue O
. O

propaganda
“ O
But O
when O
we O
ask O
families O
why O
do O
they O
homeschool O
, O
near O
the O
top O
nowadays O
is O
concern O
about O
the O
environment O
of O
schools O
, O
and O
that O
includes O
safety O
, O
pressure O
to O
get O
into O
drugs O
, O
pressure O
to O
get O
into O
sexual O
activity O
. O

non_propaganda
Now O
, O
he O
’ O
s O
the O
National O
Security O
Advisor O
. O

propaganda
Hitler B-PERSON
annihilated O
400,000 B-CARDINAL
Germans B-NORP
who O
were O
handicapped O
or O
suffered O
from O
chronic O
diseases O
. O

propaganda
In O
this O
extremely O
dramatic O
moment O
for O
the B-ORG
universal I-ORG
Church I-ORG
, O
he O
must O
acknowledge O
his O
mistakes O
and O
, O
in O
keeping O
with O
the O
proclaimed O
principle O
of O
zero B-CARDINAL
tolerance O
, O
Pope B-PERSON
Francis I-PERSON
must O
be O
the O
first B-ORDINAL
to O
set O
a O
good O
example O
for O
cardinals O
and O
bishops O
who O
covered O
up O
McCarrick B-ORG
’ I-ORG
s I-ORG
abuses O
and O
resign O
along O
with O
all O
of O
them O
. O

non_propaganda
Of O
course O
, O
the O
Twitterverse B-PRODUCT
is O
busy O
commenting O
on O
the O
irony O
: O
how O
a O
man O
expressing O
grave O
concerns O
that O
there O
is O
an O
atmosphere O
of O
fear O
of O
being O
punished O
for O
expressing O
grave O
concerns O
, O
was O
immediately O
fired O
. O

non_propaganda
Strzok O
has O
argued O
that O
he O
was O
just O
trying O
to O
reassure O
Page O
that O
Trump B-PERSON
couldn O
’ O
t O
win O
, O
and O
that O
he O
wasn O
’ O
t O
implying O
that O
they O
would O
take O
action O
to O
stop O
his O
election O
. O

non_propaganda
In O
the O
metaphysical O
order O
, O
penalty O
is O
a O
consequence O
of O
dependence O
on O
the O
supreme O
will O
, O
dependence O
which O
exists O
in O
the O
deepest O
recesses O
of O
created O
being O
. O

non_propaganda
Present O
Problems O
: O
Only B-CARDINAL
one I-CARDINAL
Carmel B-PERSON
functions O
fully O
autonomously O
in O
the O
Netherlands B-GPE
. O

non_propaganda
Mohammad B-PERSON
- I-PERSON
Javad I-PERSON
Larijani I-PERSON
, O
an O
international O
affairs O
assistant O
in O
the O
Iran B-GPE
’ O
s O
judiciary O
, O
disclosed O
in O
Farsi B-LANGUAGE
- O
language O
remarks O
broadcast O
on O
Iran B-GPE
’ O
s O
state O
- O
controlled O
television O
that O
Iranian B-NORP
intelligence O
officials O
secretly O
helped O
provide O
the O
al B-ORG
Qaeda I-ORG
attackers O
with O
passage O
and O
gave O
them O
refuge O
in O
the B-GPE
Islamic I-GPE
Republic I-GPE
, O
according O
to O
an O
English B-NORP
translation O
published O
by O
Al B-PERSON
Arabiya I-PERSON
. O

propaganda
She O
also O
admits O
ongoing O
discussions O
among O
these O
people O
about O
meeting O
to O
give O
grieving O
Hillary B-PERSON
Clinton I-PERSON
supporters O
hugs O
after O
Trump B-PERSON
crushed O
her O
on O
election B-DATE
day I-DATE
. O

propaganda
And O
if O
He O
is O
God O
, O
we O
must O
give O
Him O
the O
adoration O
of O
God O
. O

non_propaganda
Men O
today B-DATE
care O
more O
of O
compromise O
( O
where O
two B-CARDINAL
men O
both O
agree O
on O
what O
they O
both O
know O
is O
wrong O
) O
and O
diplomacy O
( O
seduction O
in O
another O
guise O
) O
in O
promoting O
anarchy O
through O
“ O
antinomianism O
” O
than O
they O
do O
the O
Law O
of O
God O
against O
the O
sins O
unto O
judgment O
that O
enslave O
men O
( O
John B-PERSON
8:34 I-PERSON
) O
. O

non_propaganda
It O
is O
the O
ninth B-ORDINAL
time O
Ebola O
has O
been O
recorded O
in O
the O
DRC B-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
Man O
who O
sold O
ammo O
to O
Las B-GPE
Vegas I-GPE
gunman O
speaks O
out O

non_propaganda
Like O
the O
secret O
to O
how O
nuns O
are O
to O
smile O
properly O
? O

non_propaganda
At O
the O
time O
I O
knew O
nothing O
of O
his O
long O
friendship O
with O
Cardinal O
Bergoglio B-PERSON
and O
of O
the O
important O
part O
he O
had O
played O
in O
his O
recent O
election O
, O
as O
McCarrick B-PERSON
himself O
would O
later O
reveal O
in O
a O
lecture O
at O
Villanova B-ORG
University I-ORG
and O
in O
an O
interview O
with O
the B-ORG
National I-ORG
Catholic I-ORG
Reporter I-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
A O
1980 B-DATE
graduate O
of O
Gaithersburg B-ORG
High I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Maryland B-GPE
, O
she O
said O
she O
has O
held O
multiple O
clearances O
for O
work O
done O
at O
the B-ORG
Treasury I-ORG
Department I-ORG
, O
U.S. B-ORG
Mint I-ORG
, O
IRS B-ORG
, O
State B-ORG
Department I-ORG
and O
Justice B-ORG
Department I-ORG
, O
among O
other O
government O
agencies O
. O

non_propaganda
And O
do O
you O
think O
this O
change O
in O
the O
Church B-ORG
came O
suddenly O
? O

propaganda
This O
is O
a O
time O
of O
repentance O
, O
of O
conversion O
, O
of O
prayers O
, O
of O
grace O
, O
to O
prepare O
the O
Church B-ORG
, O
the O
bride O
of O
the O
Lamb B-PERSON
, O
ready O
to O
fight O
and O
win O
with O
Mary B-PERSON
the O
battle O
against O
the O
old O
dragon O
. O

non_propaganda
He O
was O
promoted O
to O
campaign O
chairman O
in O
May B-DATE
2016 I-DATE
. O

non_propaganda
It O
moves O
the O
minds O
of O
the O
faithful O
in O
a O
Protestant B-NORP
[ O
direction O
] O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
email O
was O
sent O
by O
Eliana B-PERSON
Murillo I-PERSON
, O
the O
former O
head O
of O
Google B-ORG
’ B-PRODUCT
s I-PRODUCT
multicultural O
marketing O
department O
. O

non_propaganda
It O
means O
that O
we O
have O
kept O
quiet O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
sexual O
assault O
allegation O
, O
which O
the O
nominee O
has O
denied O
, O
has O
upended O
his O
seemingly O
sure O
- O
bet O
confirmation O
and O
only O
increased O
the O
stakes O
for O
the O
key O
lawmakers O
. O

non_propaganda
Of O
all O
people O
, O
we O
had O
assumed O
that O
Benedict B-PERSON
XVI I-PERSON
took O
the O
papacy O
seriously O
. O

non_propaganda
Obviously O
, O
the O
first B-ORDINAL
to O
have O
been O
informed O
of O
the O
measures O
taken O
by O
Pope O
Benedict B-PERSON
was O
McCarrick B-PERSON
’ O
s O
successor O
in O
Washington B-GPE
See O
, O
Cardinal O
Donald B-PERSON
Wuerl I-PERSON
, O
whose O
situation O
is O
now O
completely O
compromised O
by O
the O
recent O
revelations O
regarding O
his O
behavior O
as O
Bishop B-ORG
of I-ORG
Pittsburgh I-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
That O
was O
Version O
No O
. O

non_propaganda
` O
` O
I O
’ O
m O
just O
telling O
you O
I O
have O
received O
what O
I O
feel O
to O
be O
and O
believe O
to O
be O
credible O
evidence O
of O
a O
possible O
terrorist O
nexus O
, O
'' O
Perry B-PERSON
said O
. O

non_propaganda
— O
Juanita O
Broaddrick O
( O
@ O
atensnut O
) O
September B-DATE
21 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2018 I-DATE

non_propaganda
When O
, O
then O
? O

non_propaganda
I O
certainly O
do O
not O
believe O
it O
was O
Pope B-PERSON
Benedict I-PERSON
, O
who O
as O
Cardinal B-PRODUCT
had O
repeatedly O
denounced O
the O
corruption O
present O
in O
the O
Church B-ORG
, O
and O
in O
the B-DATE
first I-DATE
months I-DATE
of O
his O
pontificate O
had O
already O
taken O
a O
firm O
stand O
against O
the O
admission O
into O
seminary O
of O
young O
men O
with O
deep O
homosexual O
tendencies O
. O

non_propaganda
Cupich B-ORG
is O
the O
very O
model O
of O
a B-PERSON
Novus I-PERSON
Ordo I-PERSON
bishop O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
conference O
is O
advocating O
measures O
to O
strengthen O
the O
regulation O
of O
gun O
sales O
and O
dealers O
, O
as O
well O
as O
ban O
assault O
weapons O
and O
large O
- O
capacity O
magazines O
. O

propaganda
With O
the O
hindsight O
of O
52 B-DATE
years I-DATE
and O
a O
great O
deal O
of O
very O
dirty O
and O
unappealing O
water O
under O
the O
Catholic B-NORP
bridge O
, O
we O
can O
see O
it O
as O
a O
kind O
of O
warning O
prophecy O
. O

propaganda
The O
Synod O
was O
convoked O
by O
Henry B-PERSON
III I-PERSON
, O
the O
German B-NORP
king O
and O
soon O
- O
to O
- O
be O
- O
crowned O
Holy B-PERSON
Roman I-PERSON
Emperor I-PERSON
, O
a O
pious O
and O
austere O
Christian B-NORP
and O
an O
exponent O
of O
the O
Cluniac B-ORG
spirit O
of O
reform O
. O

propaganda
Irony O
of O
ironies O
, O
the O
latter O
- O
day O
Pharisees O
and O
legalists O
Francis B-PERSON
sees O
around O
every O
corner O
are O
hard O
at O
work O
defending O
Amoris B-PERSON
Laetitia I-PERSON
at O
the O
very O
moment O
it O
is O
being O
cited O
by O
bishop O
after O
bishop O
as O
their O
sole O
authority O
for O
admitting O
public O
adulterers O
to O
Holy B-ORG
Communion I-ORG
-- O
-while O
Francis O
does O
nothing O
but O
approve O
. O

propaganda
How O
can O
we O
know O
? O

non_propaganda
“ O
We O
have O
a O
firefighter O
’ O
s O
wife O
at O
this O
event O
who O
is O
pinned O
down O
behind O
the O
bar O
at O
Mandalay B-LOC
Bay I-LOC
. O

non_propaganda
So O
why O
do O
they O
now O
say O
, O
as O
Mgr B-PERSON
. O

propaganda
Breitbart B-ORG
News I-ORG
has O
exclusively O
published O
several O
of O
Epstein O
’ O
s O
reports O
, O
including O
a O
recent O
one B-CARDINAL
showing O
that O
Google B-ORG
search O
manipulation O
can O
swing O
huge O
swaths O
of O
voters O
. O

propaganda
Snowden O
then O
asked O
, O
“ O
Are O
these O
really O
the O
values O
the O
US B-GPE
should O
be O
promoting O
? O

non_propaganda
Simple O
. O

propaganda
This O
is O
a O
smear O
, O
plain O
and O
simple O
. O

non_propaganda
Then O
they O
came O
for O
trade O
unionists O
, O
but O
he O
didn O
’ O
t O
speak O
up O
because O
that O
didn O
’ O
t O
concern O
him O
. O

non_propaganda
“ O
It O
is O
most O
likely O
that O
they O
arise O
from O
an O
instability O
in O
the O
sheared O
eastward O
and O
westward O
winds O
. O
” O

non_propaganda
What O
’ O
s O
At O
Stake O
in O
the O
Fight O
For O
Religious O
Freedom O

non_propaganda
For O
rulers O
are O
not O
a O
terror O
to O
the O
good O
work O
, O
but O
to O
the O
evil O
. O

non_propaganda
Native O
- O
born O
American B-NORP
employment O
growth O
is O
represented O
by O
the O
black O
line O
, O
immigrant O
employment O
growth O
is O
in O
pink O
, O
and O
NVAWDI O
— O
the O
ratio O
of O
immigrant O
to O
native O
- O
born O
American B-NORP
job O
growth O
— O
is O
in O
blue O
. O

propaganda
DB O
: O
In O
the O
library O
, O
silence O
is O
golden O
. O

non_propaganda
“ O
What O
is O
the O
relationship O
between O
Christ O
and O
Satan O
? O

non_propaganda
Therefore O
, O
these O
sections O
of O
the O
rubric O
should O
be O
amended O
. O

non_propaganda
We O
don O
’ O
t O
remember O
those O
who O
were O
too O
intimidated O
and O
uncertain O
to O
rise O
against O
anti O
- O
Semitism O
when O
they O
saw O
it O
and O
heard O
it O
. O

non_propaganda
According O
to O
the B-ORG
Washington I-ORG
Post I-ORG
, O
“ O
Ford B-ORG
said O
she O
told O
no O
one O
of O
the O
incident O
in O
any O
detail O
until O
2012 B-DATE
, O
when O
she O
was O
in O
couples O
therapy O
with O
her O
husband O
. O
” O

non_propaganda
Ford B-ORG
has O
asked O
me O
to O
let O
you O
know O
that O
she O
appreciates O
the O
various O
options O
you O
have O
suggested O
. O

non_propaganda
“ O
I O
thought O
this O
acknowledgement O
was O
very O
important O
and O
I O
really O
did O
appreciate O
that O
he O
clarified O
the O
matter O
, O
” O
he O
said O
. O

non_propaganda
Recommendations O
include O
further O
informing O
Congress B-ORG
about O
future O
negotiations O
with O
Iran B-GPE
, O
requiring O
the B-ORG
Treasury I-ORG
Department I-ORG
to O
give O
notice O
of O
specific O
licenses O
, O
reviewing O
all O
Iran B-GPE
deal O
- O
related O
licenses O
, O
and O
increasing O
policing O
of O
US B-GPE
sanctions O
policies O
. O

non_propaganda
When O
he O
first B-ORDINAL
put O
up O
WikiLeaks B-PERSON
, O
he O
wrote O
that O
the O
whole O
idea O
of O
transparency O
, O
honoring O
people O
’ O
s O
right O
to O
know O
, O
was O
the O
central O
aim O
of O
the O
website O
. O

non_propaganda
He O
was O
not O
immediately O
available O
for O
comment O
. O

non_propaganda
Heavy O
surveillance O

non_propaganda
Kavanaugh O
’ O
s O
friend O
, O
who O
has O
not O
been O
identified O
, O
did O
not O
outright O
deny O
the O
woman O
’ O
s O
claims O
but O
told O
the B-ORG
New I-ORG
Yorker I-ORG
he O
has O
“ O
no O
recollection O
of O
that O
. O
” O

propaganda
How O
about O
acting O
on O
principle O
for O
a O
change O
and O
shoot O
the O
alligator O
. O

propaganda
“ O
Because O
when O
she O
does O
, O
she O
is O
going O
to O
look O
like O
the O
loon O
she O
is O
. O

non_propaganda
Democratize O
SSMU O
had O
targeted O
Lew B-PERSON
and O
the O
other O
two B-CARDINAL
students O
on O
the O
board O
because O
they O
had O
connections O
to O
the O
Canadian B-NORP
Jewish O
Political O
Affairs O
Committee O
( O
CJPAC O
) O
and O
were O
involved O
in O
getting O
the O
BDS B-ORG
ban O
passed O
, O
which O
Democratize O
SSMU O
claimed O
were O
“ O
conflicts O
of O
interests O
. O
” O

non_propaganda
Until O
the O
Church B-ORG
and O
her O
bishops O
get O
back O
to O
reaffirming O
traditional O
Catholic B-NORP
teaching O
on O
human O
sexuality O
we O
can O
forget O
about O
seeing O
an O
end O
to O
the O
sexual O
abuse O
crisis O
and O
the O
massive O
problem O
of O
homosexuality O
in O
the O
clergy O
. O

non_propaganda
19:21 B-CARDINAL
) O
. O

propaganda
To O
make O
matters O
worse O
( O
if O
that O
is O
even O
possible O
) O
, O
evidence O
has O
surfaced O
that O
indicates O
that O
a O
bishop O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
priests O
and O
laity O
, O
had O
brought O
the O
allegations O
about O
misconduct O
with O
seminarians O
to O
the O
attention O
of O
Church B-ORG
authorities O
but O
to O
no O
avail O
: O
Archbishop B-PERSON
McCarrick I-PERSON
was O
nonetheless O
“ O
promoted O
” O
to O
become O
the O
archbishop O
in O
our O
nation O
’ O
s O
capital O
, O
and O
elevated O
to O
the B-ORG
College I-ORG
of I-ORG
Cardinals I-ORG
. O

propaganda
And O
at O
a B-DATE
later I-DATE
date I-DATE
, O
he O
assured O
us O
that O
that O
had O
been O
done O
. O
” O
Juan B-PERSON
Carlos I-PERSON
Cruz I-PERSON
, O
the O
Karadima B-PERSON
victim O
whose O
membership O
on O
the B-ORG
Commission I-ORG
the I-ORG
Vatican I-ORG
had O
blocked O
, O
told O
AP B-ORG
, O
“ O
Cardinal B-PRODUCT
O I-PRODUCT
’ I-PRODUCT
Malley B-PERSON
called O
me O
after O
the O
pope O
’ O
s O
visit O
here O
in O
Philadelphia B-GPE
and O
he O
told O
me O
, O
among O
other O
things O
, O
that O
he O
had O
given O
the O
letter O
to O
the O
pope O
– O
in O
his O
hands O
. O
” O

non_propaganda
Some O
have O
permanent O
hearing O
loss O
or O
concussions O
, O
while O
others O
suffered O
nausea O
, O
headaches O
and O
ear O
- O
ringing O
. O

non_propaganda
They O
thought O
he O
was O
just O
some O
kind O
of O
a O
circus O
sideshow O
act O
. O

non_propaganda
Mnuchin B-ORG
tweeted O
the O
decision O
after O
meeting O
with O
President O
Donald B-PERSON
Trump I-PERSON
and O
Secretary O
of O
State B-ORG
Michael B-PERSON
R. I-PERSON
Pompeo I-PERSON
at O
the B-FAC
White I-FAC
House I-FAC
. O

non_propaganda
I O
have O
lost O
my O
diocese O
. O

non_propaganda
San B-GPE
Francisco I-GPE
is O
not O
likely O
to O
hand O
the O
felon O
over O
to O
ICE O
for O
deportation O
. O

non_propaganda
As O
my O
friend O
said O
, O
maybe O
“ O
it O
’ O
s O
going O
to O
become O
harder O
and O
harder O
for O
men O
of O
conscience O
and O
position O
to O
sit O
on O
the O
fence O
, O
” O
assuming O
there O
are O
any O
left O
. O

non_propaganda
He O
added O
that O
he O
would O
be O
more O
` O
` O
comfortable O
'' O
with O
an O
FBI B-ORG
investigation O
. O

propaganda
Meanwhile O
, O
Trump B-PERSON
took O
to O
Twitter O
early O
Tuesday O
morning B-TIME
to O
note O
the B-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Justice I-ORG
’ O
s O
inaction O
over O
the O
fact O
that O
disgraced O
anti O
- O
Trump O
FBI O
agent O
Peter B-PERSON
Strzok I-PERSON
and O
his O
mistress O
were O
engaged O
in O
a O
“ O
media O
leak O
strategy O
” O
to O
plant O
negative O
stories O
which O
were O
then O
used O
to O
secure O
FISA B-ORG
warrants O
to O
spy O
on O
the O
Trump B-PRODUCT
campaign O
. O

non_propaganda
South B-GPE
Korea I-GPE
’ O
s O
new O
president O
, O
Moon B-PERSON
Jae I-PERSON
- I-PERSON
in I-PERSON
, O
demanded O
that O
his O
nation O
be O
consulted O
before O
any O
military O
action O
. O

non_propaganda
Again O
, O
right O
now O
there O
is O
a O
lot O
of O
justified O
anger O
and O
passion O
coming O
from O
many O
holy O
and O
faithful O
lay O
people O
and O
clerics O
across O
the O
country O
, O
calling O
for O
real O
reform O
and O
“ O
house O
cleaning O
” O
of O
this O
type O
of O
depravity O
. O

propaganda
It O
was O
at O
this O
early O
“ O
no O
evidence O
” O
comment O
on O
the O
plane O
home O
from O
Rio B-GPE
that O
some O
of O
those O
paying O
attention O
started O
to O
understand O
that O
Bergoglio B-PERSON
’ O
s O
policy O
is O
in O
line O
with O
that O
of O
certain O
leaders O
of O
the O
past O
who O
recommended O
that O
if O
a O
politician O
was O
going O
to O
lie O
, O
he O
should O
lie O
big O
and O
lie O
brazenly O
. O

propaganda
` O
` O
He O
is O
very O
talented O
, O
'' O
Trump B-PERSON
said O
, O
citing O
Kim B-PERSON
's O
ability O
to O
` O
` O
take O
over O
a O
situation O
like O
he O
did O
at O
26 B-DATE
years I-DATE
of I-DATE
age I-DATE
and O
run O
it O
, O
and O
run O
it O
tough O
. O
'' O

non_propaganda
But O
it O
is O
precisely O
Christian B-NORP
doctrine O
… O
that O
frees O
people O
from O
worldly O
ideologies O
and O
assures O
that O
they O
are O
actually O
preaching O
and O
teaching O
the O
authentic O
, O
life O
- O
giving O
Gospel B-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
It O
is O
a O
great O
disservice O
to O
the O
Church B-ORG
to O
maintain O
the O
pretense O
that O
there O
is O
nothing O
problematical O
about O
AL B-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
And O
outside O
it O
. O

propaganda
She O
is O
seeking O
to O
slander O
a O
man O
's O
character O
for O
something O
she O
can O
not O
prove O
that O
she O
claims O
happened O
over O
36 B-DATE
years I-DATE
ago I-DATE
. O

non_propaganda
Carballo O
was O
Francis B-PERSON
’ O
very O
first O
appointment O
, O
April B-DATE
6 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2013 I-DATE
, O
three B-DATE
weeks I-DATE
after O
the O
Conclave B-ORG
and O
it O
was O
to O
him O
that O
the O
pope O
gave O
the O
task O
of O
the O
destruction O
of O
the O
FFIs O
, O
and O
a O
major O
part O
of O
that O
operation O
was O
to O
separate O
the O
FFIs O
from O
real O
assets O
valued O
at O
about B-CARDINAL
30 I-CARDINAL
million I-CARDINAL
Euros O
. O

non_propaganda
He O
said O
Saudi B-NORP
leaders O
made O
a O
commitment O
“ O
to O
hold O
anyone O
connected O
to O
any O
wrongdoing O
that O
may O
be O
found O
accountable O
for O
that O
, O
whether O
they O
are O
a O
senior O
officer O
or O
official O
. O
” O
He O
said O
they O
made O
“ O
no O
exceptions O
, O
” O
including O
presumably O
members O
of O
the O
royal O
family O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
duration O
is O
3 B-DATE
to I-DATE
4 I-DATE
days I-DATE
and O
they O
take O
place O
every O
time O
in O
a O
different O
Monastery O
of O
the O
Association B-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
They O
use O
rigorous O
protocols O
to O
protect O
medical O
personnel O
with O
disposable O
full O
- O
body O
suits O
, O
masks O
, O
goggles O
and O
gloves O
and O
disinfecting O
sprays O
. O

non_propaganda
Long O
before O
the O
arrival O
of O
Bergoglio B-GPE
in O
Rome B-GPE
, O
the O
successive O
Vatican B-WORK_OF_ART
Secretaries I-WORK_OF_ART
of I-WORK_OF_ART
State I-WORK_OF_ART
, O
Angelo B-PERSON
Sodano I-PERSON
and O
Tarcisio B-ORG
Bertone I-ORG
, O
were O
instrumental O
in O
advancing O
the O
homosexual O
corruption O
of O
the B-LOC
Novus I-LOC
Ordo I-LOC
establishment O
. O

non_propaganda
I O
will O
hold O
the O
priests O
of O
the O
diocese O
to O
their O
promise O
to O
live O
a O
chaste O
and O
celibate O
life O
of O
service O
to O
you O
and O
your O
parish O
, O
and O
evidence O
of O
failure O
in O
this O
regard O
will O
be O
justly O
addressed O
; O

non_propaganda
Expectations O
were O
high O
in O
2014 B-DATE
when O
the O
Pope O
created O
the O
abuse O
commission O
. O

non_propaganda
He O
needed O
an O
insurance O
policy O
. O

propaganda
But O
we O
can O
certainly O
think O
of O
many O
, O
many O
who O
spent O
their O
lives O
and O
vocations O
blatantly O
denying O
and O
undermining O
the O
Catholic B-NORP
Faith O
– O
academic O
theologians O
, O
religious O
, O
priests O
, O
bishops O
and O
cardinals O
around O
the O
world O
– O
with O
never O
a O
peep O
of O
protest O
from O
Rome B-GPE
. O

propaganda
How O
willing O
they O
are O
to O
overlook O
judgment O
when O
it O
comes O
to O
the O
criminals O
that O
run O
rampant O
in O
this O
country O
, O
and O
on O
the O
other O
hand O
how O
willing O
they O
are O
to O
show O
compassion O
to O
the O
criminals O
while O
overlooking O
the O
victims O
. O

propaganda
Enough O
is O
enough O
! O
! O
! O

propaganda
Specifically O
, O
the O
statement O
that O
Obama B-ORG
wanted O
“ O
to O
know O
everything O
we O
’ O
re O
doing O
” O
came O
in O
a O
private O
Sept. B-DATE
2 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2016 I-DATE
, O
text O
message O
from O
FBI B-ORG
lawyer O
Lisa B-PERSON
Page I-PERSON
to O
FBI B-ORG
agent O
Peter B-PERSON
Strzok I-PERSON
, O
with O
whom O
she O
was O
having O
an O
extramarital O
affair O
at O
the O
time O
. O

propaganda
And O
yet O
, O
nearly B-DATE
a I-DATE
month I-DATE
after O
the B-GPE
Las I-GPE
Vegas I-GPE
Strip I-GPE
experienced O
the O
worst O
mass O
shooting O
in O
modern O
American B-NORP
history O
, O
local O
and O
federal O
authorities O
are O
refusing O
to O
fill O
in O
the O
blanks O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
spirit O
of O
aggiornamento O
quickly O
spread O
through O
the O
Church B-ORG
in O
the B-DATE
1960s I-DATE
– O
and O
the O
seminaries O
especially O
. O

propaganda
Democrats B-NORP
Want O
Us O
To O
Believe O
All O
Women O
… O
Unless O
They O
’ O
re O
Accusing O
Keith B-PERSON
Ellison I-PERSON
, O
Bill B-PERSON
Clinton I-PERSON
, O
Al B-PERSON
Franken I-PERSON
Or O
George B-PERSON
Soros I-PERSON

non_propaganda
[ O
… O
] O
“ O
That O
is O
when O
the B-LAW
Final I-LAW
Solution I-LAW
began O
. O

non_propaganda
Cruz B-PERSON
described O
how O
the O
abuse O
was O
witnessed O
and O
covered O
up O
by O
Juan B-PERSON
Barros I-PERSON
, O
a O
priest O
whose O
appointment O
as O
a O
bishop O
in O
2015 B-DATE
prompted O
huge O
protests O
in O
Chile B-GPE
. O

propaganda
Converts O
to O
the O
prevailing O
conciliar O
religion O
and O
its O
“ O
New O
Pentecost O
” O
would O
in O
fact O
argue O
in O
this O
wise O
, O
perhaps O
citing O
the O
Council B-ORG
’ O
s O
famous O
declaration O
in O
Gaudium B-ORG
et I-ORG
Spes I-ORG
that O
, O
“ O
Thanks O
to O
the O
experience O
of O
past O
ages O
... O
the O
nature O
of O
man O
himself O
is O
more O
clearly O
revealed O
and O
new O
roads O
to O
truth O
are O
opened O
, O
” O
and O
the O
world O
now O
has O
“ O
a O
keener O
awareness O
of O
human O
dignity O
” O
( O
44 O
, O
73 O
) O
. O

non_propaganda
Why O
would O
he O
choose O
to O
walk O
away O
knowing O
that O
his O
task O
was O
not O
completed O
? O

non_propaganda
They O
have O
also O
paid O
$ O
400,000 B-MONEY
to O
the B-GPE
United I-GPE
States I-GPE
to O
settle O
a O
related O
civil O
suit O
. O

propaganda
Yet O
there O
is O
little O
doubt O
they O
will O
continue O
the O
same O
polemic O
that O
for O
nearly B-DATE
sixty I-DATE
years I-DATE
has O
doggedly O
defended O
every O
one O
of O
the O
ruinous O
“ O
reforms O
” O
that O
have O
resulted O
in O
a O
debacle O
without O
equal O
in O
Church B-ORG
history O
, O
even O
considering O
the O
Arian B-NORP
crisis O
of O
the B-DATE
4th I-DATE
century I-DATE
. O

non_propaganda
Email O
* O

non_propaganda
This O
Pope O
’ O
s O
plan O
of O
promulgating O
a O
deliberately O
ambiguous O
document O
whose O
heterodox O
interpretation O
and O
application O
he O
would O
later O
approve O
with O
a O
series O
of O
sub O
- O
magisterial O
winks O
and O
nods O
, O
both O
oral O
and O
written O
, O
is O
the O
reason O
I O
signed O
onto O
the O
Correctio B-PERSON
Filialis I-PERSON
. O

non_propaganda
Also O
be O
aware O
that O
there O
a O
few O
racial O
slurs O
in O
the O
video O
. O

non_propaganda
There O
are O
thousands B-CARDINAL
of O
predominantly O
young O
men O
marching O
towards O
the O
border O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
persecution O
of O
this O
man O
by O
huge O
media O
organizations O
which O
have O
drawn O
great O
benefit O
from O
WikiLeaks B-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
Meanwhile O
, O
the O
UK B-GPE
banned O
three B-CARDINAL
bishops O
from O
areas O
of O
Iraq B-GPE
and O
Syria B-GPE
where O
Christians B-NORP
are O
persecuted O
from O
entering O
the O
country O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
memo O
said O
the O
CHA B-ORG
possesses O
voluminous O
evidence O
, O
including O
, O
“ O
Interview O
notes O
with O
House B-ORG
Members O
’ O
Chiefs O
of O
Staff O
, O
” O
and O
“ O
Logon O
activity O
and O
computer O
access O
logs O
. O
” O
Prosecutors O
have O
not O
brought O
charges O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
pictures O
were O
published O
by O
numerous O
news O
outlets O
and O
shared O
by O
millions B-CARDINAL
of O
people O
on O
social O
media O
. O

non_propaganda
Yet O
she O
claims O
to O
be O
absolutely O
certain O
that O
Kavanaugh B-ORG
, O
whom O
she O
presumably O
knew O
only O
as O
an O
acquaintance O
and O
said O
she O
had O
not O
spoken O
to O
since O
the B-TIME
night I-TIME
the O
incident O
allegedly O
occurred O
, O
was O
involved O
in O
the O
alleged O
incident O
. O

non_propaganda
Ali B-PERSON
admitted O
to O
having O
fought O
with O
Jihadists B-NORP
in O
Syria B-GPE
. O

non_propaganda
They O
might O
explain O
that O
to O
Ohio B-GPE
, O
Michigan B-GPE
and O
Pennsylvania B-GPE
. O

propaganda
The B-GPE
United I-GPE
States I-GPE
Conference I-GPE
of I-GPE
Mayors I-GPE
passed O
several O
resolutions O
last B-DATE
week I-DATE
that O
called O
for O
more O
gun O
confiscation O
legislation O
following O
all O
the O
debate O
about O
guns O
after O
several O
shootings O
, O
despite O
the O
fact O
that O
government O
has O
never O
been O
given O
authority O
to O
restrict O
or O
regulate O
arms O
. O

non_propaganda
Mr. O
Garcia B-PERSON
Zarate I-PERSON
had O
been O
homeless O
at O
the O
time O
of O
the O
shooting O
and O
had O
multiple O
felony O
convictions O
and O
five B-CARDINAL
prior O
deportations O
to O
Mexico B-GPE
. O

propaganda
If O
you O
want O
the O
FBI B-ORG
to O
go O
back O
that O
far O
@ O
[ O
email O
protected O
] O
to O
investigate O
Ford B-ORG
’ O
s O
allegations O
… O
. O

non_propaganda
Habib B-PERSON
- I-PERSON
Powell I-PERSON
had O
attended O
the O
Iftar B-ORG
dinner O
with O
members O
of O
Muslim B-ORG
Brotherhood I-ORG
front O
groups O
. O

non_propaganda
As O
a O
consequence O
, O
the O
two B-CARDINAL
pontifical O
documents O
are O
to O
be O
held O
as O
normative O
in O
force O
for O
monasteries O
of O
nuns O
and O
must O
be O
read O
in O
a O
unitary O
vision O
. O

propaganda
Amazingly O
, O
more O
Ecuadorean B-ORG
Government I-ORG
documents O
have O
just O
been O
discovered O
for O
the O
Guardian B-ORG
, O
this O
time O
spy O
agency O
reports O
detailing O
visits O
of O
Paul B-PERSON
Manafort I-PERSON
and O
unspecified O
“ O
Russians B-NORP
” O
to O
the O
Embassy B-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
Wait O
! O

propaganda
They O
care O
more O
about O
the O
approbation O
and O
favor O
of O
men O
than O
they O
do O
that O
of O
the O
Living O
God O
and O
what O
His O
Word O
declares O
( O
Galatians O
1:10 B-TIME
) O
, O
not O
knowing O
that O
which O
his O
highly O
favored O
among O
men O
is O
an O
abomination O
unto O
the O
Lord O
( O
Luke B-PERSON
16:15 O
) O
. O

non_propaganda
Unbeknownst O
to O
him O
, O
the O
court O
reporter O
inadvertently O
kept O
a O
recording O
of O
the O
meeting O
that O
ultimately O
came O
to O
light O
. O

non_propaganda
Who O
was O
this O
victim O
? O

non_propaganda
Police O
believe O
Douglas B-PERSON
Haig I-PERSON
may O
have O
conspired O
with O
gunman O
Stephen B-PERSON
Paddock I-PERSON
, O
but O
it O
's O
unclear O
if O
he O
's O
still O
under O
investigation O
. O

propaganda
The O
Guardian B-ORG
had O
to O
publish O
an O
apology O
. O

non_propaganda
One B-CARDINAL
of O
the O
world O
’ O
s O
most O
renowned O
theologians O
, O
Fr O
. O

non_propaganda
WaPo B-ORG
reports O
: O

non_propaganda
And O
he O
said O
, O
If O
I O
find O
there O
forty B-DATE
and O
five B-CARDINAL
, O
I O
will O
not O
destroy O
it O
. O

non_propaganda
6 B-CARDINAL
– O
There O
are O
crossover O
connections O
between O
employees O
paid O
by O
Powell B-PERSON
’ O
s O
10,000 O
Women O
and O
the O
Clintons B-PERSON
. O

non_propaganda
Luckily O
, O
he O
was O
the O
only O
judge O
on O
the O
panel O
to O
think O
this O
. O

non_propaganda
“ O
We O
take O
anti O
- O
Semitism O
quite O
seriously O
, O
” O
J O
Street O
’ O
s O
statement O
read O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
behavior O
of O
several O
of O
the O
Democratic B-NORP
members O
of O
this O
committee O
at O
my O
hearing O
a B-DATE
few I-DATE
weeks I-DATE
ago I-DATE
was O
an O
embarrassment O
. O

non_propaganda
Criminals O
put O
to O
death O
undergo O
a O
penalty O
no O
different O
from O
the O
one O
exacted O
from O
the O
most O
innocent O
amongst O
us O
. O

non_propaganda
Yet O
, O
there O
is O
no O
outcry O
from O
the O
community O
, O
not O
from O
Muslims B-NORP
, O
not O
from O
non B-NORP
- I-NORP
Muslims I-NORP
. O

non_propaganda
Perhaps O
someone O
gave O
the O
pope O
an O
injection O
, O
a O
drug O
, O
and O
he O
is O
not O
responsible O
. O

non_propaganda
It O
should O
be O
clear O
by O
now O
that O
the O
entire O
official O
narrative O
surrounding O
the O
Las B-GPE
Vegas I-GPE
shooting O
that O
left O
59 B-CARDINAL
people O
dead O
and O
hundreds B-CARDINAL
injured O
is O
falling O
apart O
. O

non_propaganda
Rather O
, O
it O
need O
only O
be O
shown O
by O
“ O
a O
preponderance O
of O
evidence O
” O
that O
the O
person O
poses O
a O
risk O
of O
injury O
to O
self O
or O
others O
. O

propaganda
In O
the O
end O
, O
Only O
the O
corrupt O
king O
acknowledges O
the O
God O
of O
Shadrach O
, O
Meshach B-PERSON
, O
and O
Abednego B-PERSON
. O

non_propaganda
Kavanaugh O
“ O
immediately O
submitted O
to O
an O
interview O
under O
penalty O
of O
felony O
for O
any O
knowingly O
false O
statements O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
security O
guard O
, O
Jesus B-PERSON
Campos I-PERSON
, O
was O
struck O
in O
the O
leg O
as O
the O
gunman O
, O
from O
behind O
his O
door O
, O
shot O
into O
the O
hallway O
on O
the O
32nd B-ORDINAL
floor O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
rounds O
he O
sold O
are O
called O
` O
` O
tracer O
ammunition O
'' O
– O
bullets O
that O
leave O
a O
visible O
trail O
when O
fired O
. O

non_propaganda
Very O
little O
is O
said O
of O
any O
efforts O
being O
made O
to O
increase O
vocational O
outreach O
using O
the O
internet O
or O
through O
diocesan O
contacts O
. O

non_propaganda
According O
to O
Fox B-ORG
News I-ORG
, O
Saucier B-ORG
argues O
that O
the O
same O
officials O
who O
sought O
out O
punishment O
to O
Saucier B-ORG
for O
his O
actions O
chose O
to O
be O
lenient O
with O
Hillary B-PERSON
Clinton I-PERSON
in O
her O
use O
of O
a O
private O
email O
server O
and O
mishandling O
of O
classified O
information O
. O

non_propaganda
Sierra B-ORG
Leone I-ORG
reported O
the O
highest O
number O
of O
Ebola O
cases O
, O
with O
nearly O
of O
all O
those O
infected O
having O
been O
residents O
of O
the O
nation O
. O

non_propaganda
Then O
the O
princes O
, O
the O
governors O
, O
and O
captains O
, O
the O
judges O
, O
the O
treasurers O
, O
the O
counsellors O
, O
the O
sheriffs O
, O
and O
all O
the O
rulers O
of O
the O
provinces O
, O
were O
gathered O
together O
unto O
the O
dedication O
of O
the O
image O
that O
Nebuchadnezzar B-PERSON
the O
king O
had O
set O
up O
; O
and O
they O
stood O
before O
the O
image O
that O
Nebuchadnezzar B-PERSON
had O
set O
up O
. O

non_propaganda
Whether O
or O
not O
the B-GPE
U. I-GPE
S. I-GPE
will O
follow O
suit O
and O
outlaw O
it O
nationally O
still O
remains O
to O
be O
seen O
. O

non_propaganda
However O
, O
scientists O
warned O
that O
it O
should O
not O
be O
assumed O
that O
the O
ultra O
- O
cooling O
of O
the O
sun O
would O
potentially O
prevent O
the O
negative O
effects O
of O
global O
warming O
. O

non_propaganda
( O
The O
exact O
message O
, O
time O
- O
stamped O
1:50 B-TIME
p.m. I-TIME
, O
reads O
` O
` O
Yes O
, O
bc O
potus O
wants O
to O
know O
everything O
we O
are O
doing O
. O
'' O
) O

non_propaganda
Grant O
? O

non_propaganda
Many O
have O
also O
speculated O
that O
, O
because O
McCarrick B-PRODUCT
’ I-PRODUCT
s I-PRODUCT
victims O
were O
overwhelmingly O
above O
the O
age O
of O
consent O
, O
the O
media O
didn O
’ O
t O
consider O
them O
newsworthy O
. O

non_propaganda
That O
monastery O
in O
Germany B-GPE
is O
lost O
. O

non_propaganda
ZMapp B-ORG
is O
also O
an O
experimental O
drug O
that O
could O
aid O
in O
the O
recovery O
from O
the O
Ebola O
virus O
. O

non_propaganda
Now O
Bible B-WORK_OF_ART
in O
the O
Schools B-NORP
is O
facing O
a O
stiff O
legal O
challenge O
. O

non_propaganda
And O
this O
after O
also O
humiliating O
Burke O
as O
the O
spiritual O
patron O
of O
the B-ORG
Knights I-ORG
of I-ORG
Malta I-ORG
, O
to O
which O
he O
was O
exiled O
after O
his O
removal O
. O

non_propaganda
For O
a O
quick O
run O
down O
of O
the O
political O
hit O
on O
Kavanaugh B-ORG
, O
take O
a O
look O
at O
this O
short O
synopsis O
by O
Paul B-PERSON
Joseph I-PERSON
Watson I-PERSON
. O

non_propaganda
America B-GPE
's O
Immigration B-ORG
Voice I-ORG
. O

propaganda
Spend O
enough O
time O
in O
Catholic B-ORG
World I-ORG
and O
you O
inevitably O
meet O
good O
men O
who O
quit O
the O
seminary O
because O
of O
some O
rampant O
( O
and O
often O
violent O
) O
depravity O
. O

propaganda
Sadly O
, O
the O
picture O
emerging O
is O
one O
that O
includes O
a O
shocking O
amount O
of O
evidence O
pointing O
towards O
a O
classic O
deep O
state O
false O
flag O
operation O
. O

non_propaganda
An O
administrative O
error O
this B-DATE
month I-DATE
revealed O
that O
the O
US B-GPE
justice O
department O
had O
secretly O
filed O
criminal O
charges O
against O
Assange B-NORP
. O

non_propaganda
“ O
During O
the O
air O
traffic O
control O
recordings O
, O
which O
were O
released O
by O
political O
strategist O
and O
co O
- O
founder O
of O
“ O
The B-WORK_OF_ART
New I-WORK_OF_ART
Right I-WORK_OF_ART
” O
Mike B-PERSON
Tokes I-PERSON
, O
one B-CARDINAL
of O
the O
dispatchers O
is O
heard O
telling O
an O
incoming O
plane O
that O
landing O
might O
not O
be O
a O
good O
idea O
because O
there O
were O
multiple O
active O
shooters O
on O
the O
airport O
property O
itself O
, O
” O
SHTFplan B-PERSON
reported O
. O

propaganda
The O
successors O
of O
the O
Apostles B-PRODUCT
, O
the O
only O
ones O
in O
a O
position O
to O
end O
his O
rampage O
, O
must O
demand O
his O
resignation O
and O
, O
should O
he O
refuse O
as O
expected O
, O
act O
in O
this O
unprecedented O
emergency O
to O
declare O
his O
removal O
from O
the O
office O
he O
has O
criminally O
abused O
and O
whose O
very O
credibility O
he O
threatens O
to O
destroy O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
emerging O
homosexual O
clergy O
scandal O
is O
just O
beginning O
to O
unfold O
. O

propaganda
It O
skewers O
them O
. O

non_propaganda
First B-ORDINAL
, O
he O
insulted O
the O
abuse O
victims O
. O

non_propaganda
Eventually O
a O
compromise O
was O
found O
in O
1971 B-DATE
when O
Pope B-ORG
Paul I-ORG
VI I-ORG
lifted O
the O
excommunications O
and O
Mindszenty B-PERSON
was O
able O
to O
leave O
the O
U.S. B-GPE
embassy O
. O

non_propaganda
It O
is O
the O
DRC B-ORG
's O
ninth B-ORDINAL
known O
outbreak O
of O
Ebola O
since O
1976 B-DATE
, O
when O
the O
deady O
viral O
disease O
was O
first B-ORDINAL
identified O
in O
then O
- O
Zaire B-GPE
by O
a O
Belgian B-NORP
- O
led O
team O
. O

non_propaganda
. O

non_propaganda
During O
the O
audience O
Bergoglio B-PERSON
queried O
: O
“ O
What O
is O
Cardinal B-PERSON
McCarrick I-PERSON
like O
? O
” O
and O
Viganò B-GPE
replied O
with O
the O
truth O
Bergoglio B-PERSON
obviously O
did O
not O
want O
to O
hear O
: O

propaganda
The O
circumstances O
pertaining O
to O
our B-DATE
day I-DATE
would O
therefore O
dictate O
a O
reassessment O
of O
the O
death O
penalty O
, O
which O
the O
new O
man O
- O
centered O
theology O
insists O
on O
viewing O
almost O
exclusively O
from O
the O
standpoint O
of O
the O
criminal O
and O
human O
society O
rather O
than O
from O
God O
’ O
s O
. O

non_propaganda
He O
said O
a O
victory O
for O
Silvio B-PERSON
Berlusconi I-PERSON
's I-PERSON
party O
in O
Italy B-GPE
's O
March B-DATE
4 I-DATE
election O
would O
strengthen O
the O
nationalist O
fold O
. O

propaganda
Where O
it O
was O
simply O
wrong O
it O
was O
ridiculous O
and O
where O
it O
was O
wrong O
and O
political O
it O
was O
outright O
wicked O
. O

non_propaganda
Here O
’ O
s O
a O
link O
for O
ya O
to O
do O
just O
that O
. O

non_propaganda
You O
don O
’ O
t O
have O
to O
look O
far O
for O
fresh O
news O
about O
Mars B-LOC
, O
Saturn B-PRODUCT
, O
or O
Jupiter B-LOC
these B-DATE
days I-DATE
, O
but O
Neptune B-FAC
doesn O
’ O
t O
always O
get O
the O
same O
kind O
of O
attention O
. O

propaganda
In O
it O
, O
Jews B-NORP
are O
described O
as O
: O
“ O
arrogant O
, O
” O
“ O
jealous O
, O
” O
“ O
selfish O
, O
” O
“ O
spiteful O
, O
” O
“ O
greedy O
, O
” O
“ O
cursed O
, O
” O
“ O
apes O
and O
swine O
, O
” O
and O
“ O
under O
divine O
displeasure O
. O
” O

non_propaganda
And O
some O
say O
this O
show O
could O
be O
quite O
spectacular O
. O

propaganda
Among O
the O
documents O
to O
be O
declassified O
are O
all O
of O
the O
text O
messages O
between O
disgraced O
FBI B-ORG
figures O
Peter B-PERSON
Strzok I-PERSON
and O
Lisa B-PERSON
Page I-PERSON
. O

propaganda
The O
scales O
have O
fallen O
from O
Fisher B-FAC
’ I-FAC
s I-FAC
eyes I-FAC
and O
now O
, O
at O
last O
, O
she O
sees O
Bergoglio B-PERSON
, O
however O
grudgingly O
, O
for O
what O
he O
is O
: O
a O
power O
- O
mad O
ecclesiastical O
tyrant O
. O

non_propaganda
All O
very O
well O
and O
good O
, O
except O
for O
the O
fact O
that O
the O
Church B-ORG
's O
constant O
and O
unchanging O
moral O
teaching O
on O
this O
makes O
no O
such O
allowance O
. O

non_propaganda
“ O
This O
puts O
a O
whole O
different O
lens O
on O
this O
outbreak O
and O
gives O
us O
increased O
urgency O
to O
move O
very O
quickly O
into O
Mbandaka B-PERSON
to O
stop O
this O
new O
first B-ORDINAL
sign O
of O
transmission O
, O
” O
he O
said O
. O

propaganda
Shapira O
ends O
his O
article O
by O
suggesting O
that O
commentators O
should O
do O
more O
complete O
research O
, O
maybe O
even O
use O
Google B-ORG
, O
before O
they O
jump O
to O
conclusions O
. O

non_propaganda
The B-ORG
Washington I-ORG
Post I-ORG
first O
reported O
on O
the O
story O
prior O
to O
Trump B-PRODUCT
’ O
s O
tweet O
. O

propaganda
In O
sum O
, O
Faggioli B-PERSON
is O
representative O
of O
the O
thinking O
that O
requires O
defense O
of O
a O
homosexualized O
clergy O
if O
only O
for O
the O
reason O
that O
tradition O
- O
minded O
Catholics B-NORP
can O
not O
be O
allowed O
to O
take O
their O
place O
: O
“ O
This O
neo O
- O
traditionalist O
Catholicism O
believes O
that O
sexual O
abuses O
are O
committed O
only O
by O
homosexual O
clergy O
… O
and O
that O
the O
crisis O
of O
abuse O
can O
be O
resolved O
by O
a O
kind O
of O
Catholic B-NORP
Jacobinism O
that O
should O
eliminate O
all O
bishops O
and O
priests O
minimally O
engaged O
in O
dialogue O
with O
modern O
culture O
, O
and O
replaced O
by O
a O
young O
clergy O
marked O
by O
personal O
sanctity O
but O
also O
by O
a O
fascination O
for O
a O
mythical O
Middle O
Ages O
and O
the O
rejection O
of O
a O
Church B-ORG
- O
world O
relationship O
based O
on O
a O
principle O
of O
reality O
. O
” O

non_propaganda
In O
addition O
, O
you O
promised O
to O
obey O
and O
be O
loyal O
to O
your O
bishop O
. O

non_propaganda
Email O
* O

non_propaganda
Meanwhile O
, O
as O
Fastiggi B-ORG
and O
Goldstein B-ORG
labor O
to O
convince O
us O
that O
nothing O
is O
amiss O
with O
AL B-ORG
, O
Pope O
Bergoglio B-PERSON
is O
sending O
clear O
signals O
of O
concern O
about O
the O
rising O
opposition O
among O
the O
faithful O
to O
his O
master O
plan O
to O
subvert O
the O
Church B-ORG
according O
to O
his O
false O
notion O
of O
mercy O
. O

propaganda
He O
will O
cling O
to O
power O
with O
his O
last O
breath O
in O
order O
to O
carry O
out O
the O
many O
other O
acts O
of O
ecclesial O
subversion O
he O
clearly O
has O
in O
mind O
. O

non_propaganda
Chile B-GPE
' O
cover O
- O
up O
' O
letter O
contradicts O
Pope O

propaganda
It O
would O
be O
nice O
to O
know O
who O
he O
is O
for O
someone O
to O
let O
him O
know O
his O
actions O
are O
not O
okay O
! O
” O
Spittler B-PERSON
added O
: O
“ O
Real O
tough O
guy O
… O
approaches O
a O
group O
of O
teenagers O
minding O
their O
own O
business O
just O
having O
a O
burger O
! O

non_propaganda
He O
should O
own O
a O
house O
or O
stand O
to O
inherit O
one O
. O

propaganda
But O
they O
will O
also O
be O
doing O
their O
sacred O
duty O
before O
God O
in O
reassuring O
their O
thoroughly O
scandalized O
flocks O
that O
they O
are O
absolutely O
committed O
to O
the O
defense O
and O
enforcement O
of O
the O
Church B-ORG
’ O
s O
moral O
teaching O
at O
a O
time O
when O
it O
is O
under O
scurrilous O
attack O
from O
within O
. O

propaganda
Today O
, O
Saudi B-GPE
Arabia I-GPE
is O
using O
these O
weapons O
to O
crush O
starving O
and O
stricken O
people O
in O
a O
genocidal O
assault O
on O
Yemen B-GPE
. O

propaganda
Our O
hopes O
and O
prayers O
are O
with O
them O
as O
the O
foremost O
instruments O
of O
divine O
providence O
in O
the O
ecclesia O
Dei O
adflicta O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
virus O
is O
handed O
on O
by O
contact O
with O
bodily O
fluids O
-- O
touching O
a O
sick O
or O
dead O
person O
is O
a O
well O
- O
known O
source O
of O
infection O
. O

non_propaganda
That O
is O
the O
school O
of O
our O
Faith O
. O

non_propaganda
Some O
members O
are O
themselves O
survivors O
of O
abuse O
, O
according O
to O
the O
statement O
, O
but O
they O
were O
not O
identified O
to O
protect O
their O
privacy O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
police O
quickly O
intervened O
to O
save O
the O
victim O
who O
lodged O
a O
complaint O
. O

propaganda
Arroyo B-ORG
spoke O
with O
Cruz B-PERSON
as O
well O
, O
who O
said O
he O
was O
“ O
incredibly O
frustrated O
” O
when O
Barros B-ORG
was O
going O
to O
be O
appointed O
. O

non_propaganda
We O
were O
all O
united O
in O
the O
praise O
of O
the O
Spirit B-ORG
who O
had O
brought O
us O
there O
together O
from O
different O
languages O
and O
nations O
. O
” O

non_propaganda
At O
one B-CARDINAL
point O
, O
as O
they O
greeted O
each O
other O
, O
Prince B-PERSON
Mohammed I-PERSON
noted O
the O
two B-CARDINAL
countries O
were O
important O
allies O
. O

non_propaganda
Heather B-PERSON
Nauert I-PERSON
, O
the O
state O
department O
spokeswoman O
, O
said O
the O
US B-GPE
embassy O
learned O
on O
Friday B-DATE
that O
the O
Guangzhou B-GPE
employee O
showed O
concussion O
symptoms O
after O
medical O
testing O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
newspaper O
account O
continues O
: O

propaganda
The O
facts O
refute O
their O
arguments O
, O
but O
beyond O
that O
, O
the B-LAW
Second I-LAW
Amendment I-LAW
recognizes O
the O
right O
to O
keep O
and O
bear O
arms O
is O
a O
right O
given O
to O
us O
by O
our O
Creator B-PERSON
, O
not O
a O
permission O
we O
gain O
from O
government O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
official O
diocesan O
newspaper O
, O
KirchenZeitung B-ORG
, O
announced O
on O
February B-DATE
9 I-DATE
that O
in O
two B-CARDINAL
different O
parishes O
in O
the O
Diocese O
of O
Linz O
homosexual O
couples O
were O
explicitly O
invited O
to O
receive O
a O
Church B-ORG
blessing O
on O
St. B-GPE
Valentine I-GPE
's I-GPE
Day I-GPE
. O

non_propaganda
The O
disease O
was O
first O
detected O
in O
1976 B-DATE
in O
two B-CARDINAL
simultaneous O
outbreaks O
, O
one O
in O
what O
is O
now O
Nzara B-GPE
, O
South B-GPE
Sudan I-GPE
, O
and O
the O
other O
in O
Yambuku B-LOC
in O
the O
DRC B-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
As O
the O
magnetic O
fields O
in O
a O
sunspot O
cross O
, O
NASA B-ORG
stated O
, O
this O
can O
cause O
a O
sudden O
energy O
explosion O
, O
also O
known O
as O
a O
solar O
flare O
. O

propaganda
In O
a O
separate O
text O
message O
to O
Page O
, O
Strzok O
wrote O
something O
cryptic O
about O
an O
“ O
insurance O
policy O
” O
in O
case O
Donald B-PERSON
Trump I-PERSON
got O
elected O
. O

non_propaganda
And O
if O
Paddock O
really O
did O
act O
alone O
and O
this O
evidence O
is O
some O
sort O
of O
mistake O
, O
there O
is O
surely O
video O
footage O
proving O
so O
. O

non_propaganda
She O
said O
she O
would O
argue O
as O
a O
child O
advocate O
that O
Barros B-ORG
was O
involved O
in O
sexual O
exploitation O
of O
children O
. O

non_propaganda
We O
’ O
ll O
stop O
it O
, O
” O
Strzok O
responded O
… O

non_propaganda
2 B-CARDINAL
p. O
229 B-CARDINAL
) O

non_propaganda
He O
is O
King O
because O
he O
is O
God O
. O

non_propaganda
Hadeed B-ORG
withdrew O
earlier O
allegations O
of O
fraud O
and O
asked O
the O
judge O
to O
try O
the O
case O
based O
solely O
on O
interpretation O
of O
contract O
language O
. O

propaganda
There O
is O
a O
kind O
of O
eerie O
silence O
around O
the O
Julian O
Assange O
case O
. O

non_propaganda
AMANA B-ORG
is O
currently O
promoting O
another O
anti O
- O
Semitic O
Duke O
- O
produced O
video O
, O
on O
the O
AMANA B-ORG
site O
. O

non_propaganda
Sheriff O
has O
said O
feds O
were O
investigating O
someone O

non_propaganda
# O
CBP B-PERSON
has O
deployed O
resources O
to O
safely O
secure O
the O
area O
near O
Imperial B-GPE
Beach I-GPE
. O

non_propaganda
NBC B-ORG
News I-ORG
reported O
that O
many O
of O
those O
in O
the O
caravan O
are O
unaccompanied O
children O
. O

propaganda
WASHINGTON B-GPE
— O
On O
an O
emergency O
mission O
to O
resolve O
a O
diplomatic O
crisis O
, O
Secretary O
of O
State B-ORG
Michael B-PERSON
R. I-PERSON
Pompeo I-PERSON
held O
delicate O
talks O
Tuesday B-DATE
with O
the O
rulers O
of O
Saudi B-GPE
Arabia I-GPE
amid O
growing O
suspicions O
that O
a O
Virginia B-GPE
- O
based O
Saudi B-NORP
columnist O
was O
killed O
on O
their O
orders O
. O

non_propaganda
Notice O
something O
else O
about O
the O
deal O
that O
Trump B-LOC
has O
presumably O
made O
with O
the O
CIA B-ORG
: O
The O
secrecy O
arrangement O
extends O
only O
to O
April B-DATE
. O

non_propaganda
At O
its O
close O
the O
number O
of O
murders O
had O
more O
than O
doubled O
, O
and O
in O
any B-DATE
six I-DATE
month I-DATE
period O
, O
more O
Americans B-NORP
were O
being O
murdered O
than O
those O
executed O
during O
the O
whole O
course O
of O
the B-DATE
century I-DATE
. O

non_propaganda
As O
the O
caravan O
approaches O
the O
US B-GPE
border O
, O
President O
Donald B-PERSON
Trump I-PERSON
has O
signed O
an O
immigration O
decree O
requiring O
asylum O
seekers O
to O
apply O
at O
their O
point O
of O
entry O
to O
the O
country O
and O
barring O
illegal O
immigrants O
from O
requesting O
asylum O
. O

non_propaganda
One B-CARDINAL
of O
its O
underground O
lairs O
was O
found O
littered O
with O
weapons O
and O
copies O
of O
the O
Qur B-PERSON
’ O
an O
. O

propaganda
The O
Central B-NORP
American I-NORP
migrant O
caravan O
has O
just O
begun O
another O
leg O
of O
their O
journey O
to O
the O
US B-GPE
border O
hastily O
reinforced O
by O
the O
Army B-ORG
and O
Marine B-ORG
Corps I-ORG
. O

propaganda
The O
craziness O
over O
transgender O
students O
and O
bathrooms O
/ O
locker O
rooms O
, O
allowing O
students O
to O
“ O
take O
a O
knee O
” O
during O
the O
playing O
of O
the O
National O
Anthem O
, O
the O
Left O
- O
wing O
curriculum O
, O
and O
refusing O
to O
allow O
students O
to O
wear O
shirts O
that O
praise O
POTUS O
Trump B-PRODUCT
or O
feature O
the O
American B-NORP
flag O
are O
also O
driving O
parents O
into O
homeschooling O
. O

non_propaganda
Donald B-PERSON
Trump I-PERSON
has O
delivered O
on O
these O
as O
well O
as O
any O
president O
since O
Reagan B-PERSON
. O

propaganda
But O
the O
skepticism O
over O
this O
story O
is O
very O
widespread O
, O
including O
among O
Assange B-PERSON
's O
most O
devoted O
haters O
, O
because O
it O
's O
so O
sketchy O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
CIA B-ORG
will O
cave O
. O

non_propaganda
Jordanian B-NORP
officials O
arrested O
Patel B-PERSON
a B-DATE
few I-DATE
days I-DATE
later I-DATE
. O

propaganda
If O
the O
Ramadan B-PERSON
imperative O
is O
to O
become O
more O
devout O
, O
the O
Muslim B-NORP
who O
applies O
himself O
diligently O
to O
the O
Ramadan O
observance O
will O
simultaneously O
become O
more O
both O
merciful O
to O
his O
fellow O
Muslims B-NORP
and O
more O
severe O
against O
the O
unbelievers O
. O

non_propaganda
Downstream O
lies O
Kinshasa B-PERSON
and O
Brazzaville B-PERSON
– O
the O
DRC B-ORG
’ O
s O
capital O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
president O
also O
pointed O
out O
that O
Donnelly B-ORG
had O
opposed O
tax O
cuts O
and O
joined O
with O
his O
fellow O
Democrats B-NORP
in O
attacking O
and O
voting O
against O
Justice O
Brett B-PERSON
Kavanaugh I-PERSON
's I-PERSON
confirmation O
to O
the B-ORG
Supreme I-ORG
Court I-ORG
. O

propaganda
Similarly O
, O
Obama B-DATE
- I-DATE
era I-DATE
national O
security O
officials O
seem O
determined O
to O
use O
the O
harshest O
possible O
language O
to O
attack O
President O
Trump B-PERSON
. O

non_propaganda
Nonetheless O
, O
it O
is O
equally O
possible O
to O
undertake O
a O
journey O
of O
discernment O
… O
. O

propaganda
Syriac B-ORG
Catholic I-ORG
Patriarch I-ORG
Ignatius O
Ephrem O
Joseph B-PERSON
III I-PERSON
Younan B-GPE
himself O
has O
in O
the O
past O
appealed O
to O
the O
West O
“ O
not O
to O
forget O
the O
Christians B-NORP
in O
the B-LOC
Middle I-LOC
East I-LOC
. O
” O
The O
former O
Melkite O
Greek O
Catholic O
Patriarch O
Gregory B-PERSON
III I-PERSON
has O
also O
said O
: O
“ O
I O
do O
not O
understand O
why O
the O
world O
does O
not O
raise O
its O
voice O
against O
such O
acts O
of O
brutality O
. O
” O

propaganda
As O
reported O
by O
The B-ORG
Washington I-ORG
Times I-ORG
, O
the O
recent O
school O
shooting O
at O
Parkland B-GPE
, O
Fla. B-GPE
, O
was O
the O
last O
straw O
for O
scores O
of O
parents O
. O

non_propaganda
Moreover O
, O
the O
Maltese B-NORP
bishops O
' O
“ O
guidelines O
” O
for O
implementing O
AL B-ORG
, O
published O
in O
L O
’ O
Osservatore O
Romano O
— O
for O
which O
Bergoglio B-PERSON
thanked O
them O
— O
declare O
thus O
: O

non_propaganda
The O
mission O
is O
scheduled O
to O
launch O
sometime O
in O
the B-DATE
first I-DATE
half I-DATE
of I-DATE
this I-DATE
year I-DATE
, O
no B-DATE
earlier I-DATE
than I-DATE
March I-DATE
. O

non_propaganda
It O
wasn O
’ O
t O
always O
like O
this O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
double O
standard O
here O
is O
pretty O
clear O
. O

non_propaganda
What O
rupture O
? O

propaganda
The O
civility O
of O
the O
Left O
on O
full O
display O
… O
pic.twitter.com/gUzBVRpP7X O
— O
The B-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Bugle I-ORG
🇺 O
🇸 B-ORG
( O
@ O
ColumbiaBugle B-ORG
) O
July B-DATE
5 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2018 I-DATE

non_propaganda
When O
I O
was O
in O
Columbia B-GPE
, O
I O
read O
in O
the O
paper O
about O
the O
change O
in O
the O
first B-ORDINAL
article O
of O
the B-LAW
Constitution I-LAW
of I-LAW
the I-LAW
Republic I-LAW
of I-LAW
Columbia I-LAW
. O

propaganda
Mr. O
Wilson B-PERSON
, O
an O
avowed O
anarchist O
who O
hopes O
for O
a O
world O
in O
which O
governments O
can O
’ O
t O
stop O
individuals O
from O
getting O
guns O
, O
claimed O
his O
First B-LAW
Amendment I-LAW
right O
to O
free O
speech O
was O
being O
violated O
. O

non_propaganda
All O
the O
cities O
in O
the O
Almoravid B-NORP
state O
were O
conquered O
by O
the O
Almohads B-PERSON
. O

non_propaganda
Instead O
, O
move O
to O
a O
location O
where O
the O
sounds O
are O
not O
present O
, O
'' O
it O
says O
, O
urging O
people O
with O
medical O
problems O
to O
consult O
a O
doctor O
. O

non_propaganda
McMaster O
subscribed O
to O
the O
Obama B-LOC
view O
that O
Islamic B-NORP
terrorism O
has O
nothing O
to O
do O
with O
Islam B-ORG
, O
despite O
the O
numerous O
Islamic B-NORP
texts O
and O
teachings O
that O
incite B-NORP
Muslims I-NORP
to O
wage O
war O
against O
unbelievers O
. O

non_propaganda
Imran B-GPE
is O
in O
court O
July B-DATE
3 I-DATE
for O
a O
possible O
plea O
deal O
in O
the O
bank O
fraud O
case O
. O

propaganda
The O
criminal O
attacker O
, O
one B-CARDINAL
Kino B-PERSON
Jimenez I-PERSON
, O
took O
the O
boy O
’ O
s O
hat O
, O
yelled O
at O
him O
, O
and O
then O
threw O
a O
drink O
in O
the O
boy O
’ O
s O
face O
before O
walking O
off O
( O
and O
stealing O

propaganda
Moreover O
, O
the O
main O
author O
of O
the O
story O
, O
Luke B-PERSON
Harding I-PERSON
, O
is O
known O
to O
be O
a O
notorious O
fraud O
, O
a O
russo O
- O
phobe O
intelligence O
asset O
with O
a O
personal O
grievance O
towards O
Assange B-NORP
and O
Wikileaks B-NORP
. O

non_propaganda
McMaster B-PERSON
is O
remaking O
it O
to O
match O
Jeb B-PERSON
Bush I-PERSON
’ O
s O
vision O
. O
” O

non_propaganda
My O
memo O
of O
December B-DATE
6 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2006 I-DATE
was O
kept O
by O
my O
superiors O
, O
and O
was O
never O
returned O
to O
me O
with O
any O
actual O
decision O
by O
the O
superiors O
on O
this O
matter O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
Pope O
’ O
s O
claim O
that O
he O
had O
never O
received O
any O
victim O
testimony O
regarding O
the O
complicity O
of O
Chilean B-PERSON
Bishop I-PERSON
Juan I-PERSON
Barros I-PERSON
in O
child O
sex O
abuse O
has O
proven O
to O
be O
false O
. O

non_propaganda
He O
was O
one O
of O
my O
professors O
in O
Patristics B-ORG
at O
Oxford B-ORG
and O
he O
was O
one O
of O
the O
most O
mild O
- O
mannered O
, O
least O
confrontational O
, O
kindest O
academics O
one O
could O
have O
hoped O
to O
meet O
. O

non_propaganda
Are O
you O
perfect O
? O

non_propaganda
Those O
changes O
can O
affect O
weather O
, O
though O
forecasting O
specific O
differences O
has O
proven O
difficult O
. O

non_propaganda
And O
why O
? O

non_propaganda
This O
reminds O
me O
of O
when O
I O
gave O
a O
prayer O
at O
the O
state O
capital O
in O
Minnesota B-GPE
. O

non_propaganda
YUMA B-GPE
, O
Ariz. B-GPE
– O
Yuma B-ORG
Sector I-ORG
Border I-ORG
Patrol I-ORG
agents O
arrested O
a O
gang O
member O
belonging O
to O
the O
Mara B-GPE
Salvatrucha-503 O
Gang B-PERSON
early O
Monday O
morning B-TIME
. O

non_propaganda
One B-CARDINAL
resident O
of O
Puerto B-GPE
Rico I-GPE
's I-GPE
Caño O
Martín B-PERSON
Peña I-PERSON
neighborhood O
, O
Gladys B-ORG
Peña I-ORG
, O
told O
the O
Herald B-PERSON
that O
her O
home O
was O
built O
by O
people O
in O
her O
neighborhood O
and O
that O
fixtures O
for O
the O
dwelling O
were O
gathered O
from O
abandoned O
structures O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
student O
, O
Ashley B-PERSON
Arnold I-PERSON
, O
is O
working O
towards O
an O
online O
sociology O
degree O
with O
the O
university O
. O

non_propaganda
It O
’ O
s O
open O
season O
on O
the O
opposition O
. O

non_propaganda
This O
is O
encouraging O
news O
. O

propaganda
Graham B-PERSON
continued O
, O
` O
` O
Would O
you O
say O
you O
' O
ve O
been O
through O
hell O
? O
'' O

non_propaganda
` O
` O
The O
medical O
indications O
are O
very O
similar O
and O
entirely O
consistent O
with O
the O
medical O
indications O
that O
have O
taken O
place O
to O
Americans B-NORP
working O
in O
Cuba B-GPE
, O
'' O
he O
said O
. O

non_propaganda
By O
Saturday B-DATE
, O
more B-CARDINAL
than I-CARDINAL
3,500 I-CARDINAL
troops O
had O
been O
deployed O
, O
including O
about B-CARDINAL
1,000 I-CARDINAL
Marines B-NORP
in O
California B-GPE
, O
the O
Pentagon B-ORG
said O
. O

non_propaganda
If O
you O
recall O
, O
the B-GPE
Islamic I-GPE
State I-GPE
has O
never O
claimed O
responsibility O
for O
attacks O
they O
were O
not O
involved O
in O
. O

non_propaganda
And O
there O
are O
many O
ways O
to O
get O
evidence O
. O

non_propaganda
In O
June B-DATE
, O
the B-ORG
Supreme I-ORG
Court I-ORG
ruled O
specifically O
on O
this O
case O
noting O
that O
collecting O
such O
information O
actually O
does O
constitute O
a O
search O
and O
therefore O
requires O
a O
warrant O
. O

non_propaganda
* O
* O
* O

non_propaganda
Rep. O
Danny B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
helped O
get O
the O
ball O
rolling O
by O
praising O
Farrakhan B-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
I O
go O
into O
the B-ORG
“ I-ORG
mental I-ORG
health I-ORG
” I-ORG
trap I-ORG
in O
more O
detail O
in O
this O
column O
: O

propaganda
The O
government O
has O
clear O
diplomatic O
and O
moral O
obligations O
to O
protect O
Australian B-NORP
citizens O
abroad O
from O
gross O
injustice O
: O
in O
Julian B-NORP
’ O
s O
case O
, O
from O
a O
gross O
miscarriage O
of O
justice O
and O
the O
extreme O
danger O
that O
await O
him O
should O
he O
walk O
out O
of O
the O
Ecuadorean B-NORP
embassy O
in O
London B-GPE
unprotected O
. O

propaganda
The O
high O
- O
stakes O
behind O
- O
the O
- O
scenes O
jockeying O
over O
the O
confirmation O
process O
continues O
. O

non_propaganda
Indeed O
, O
their O
“ O
proposed O
alternate O
translation O
” O
reduces O
the O
avoidance O
of O
adulterous O
relations O
in O
“ O
second B-ORDINAL
marriages O
” O
to O
the O
“ O
perfect O
objective O
model O
. O
” O
Now O
, O
how O
could O
anyone O
but O
a O
Pharisee B-GPE
expect O
perfection O
from O
people O
living O
in O
adultery O
? O

non_propaganda
Roughly O
speaking O
there O
is O
a O
4-to-4 O
liberal O
to O
conservative O
ideological O
split O
on O
the O
court O
. O

non_propaganda
The B-ORG
Catholic I-ORG
Church I-ORG
's I-ORG
new O
- O
found O
` O
` O
climate O
of O
tolerance O
'' O
is O
exactly O
what O
McCarrick B-ORG
and O
company O
are O
counting O
on O
! O

propaganda
As O
for O
the O
nonsensical O
call O
to O
ban O
armor O
- O
piercing O
bullets O
, O
virtually O
every O
caliber O
of O
bullet O
, O
except O
maybe O
a O
.22 O
can O
pierce O
kevlar O
- O
based O
vests O
, O
and O
if O
you O
are O
using O
.22 O
magnums O
, O
they O
will O
even O
pierce O
those O
! O

non_propaganda
The O
signatories O
plea O
is O
that O
the O
pope O
will O
“ O
quickly O
convene O
a O
synod O
on O
the O
dangers O
of O
Islam B-ORG
. O
” O

non_propaganda
Since O
2001 B-DATE
, O
Cardinal B-PERSON
Ratzinger I-PERSON
and O
later O
as O
Pope O
Benedict B-PERSON
installed O
effective O
procedural O
reforms O
on O
clerical O
sexual O
abuse O
; O
Francis B-PERSON
in O
his O
short O
five B-DATE
years I-DATE
has O
all O
but O
completely O
dismantled O
or O
reversed O
those O
changes O
. O

propaganda
The O
only O
answer O
that O
comes O
to O
mind O
is O
that O
Jesus B-PERSON
wants O
to O
manifest O
just O
how O
weak O
is O
the O
faith O
of O
many O
within O
the O
Church B-ORG
, O
even O
among O
too O
many O
of O
her O
bishops O
. O

non_propaganda
Border B-ORG
Patrol I-ORG
has O
not O
confirmed O
whether O
this O
group O
is O
part O
of O
the O
caravan O
. O
STORY O
: O
http O
: O
//via.kswbtv.com O
/ O
Ky5E4 O
Posted O
by O
FOX B-ORG
5 O
San B-GPE
Diego I-GPE
on O
Tuesday B-DATE
, I-DATE
November I-DATE
13 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2018 I-DATE

non_propaganda
Email O
* O

non_propaganda
Iran B-GPE
Admits O
To O
Aiding O
Al O
- O
Qaeda O
and O
Facilitating B-ORG
9/11 I-ORG
Jihad I-ORG
Terror I-ORG
Attacks I-ORG

propaganda
And O
she O
was O
quoted O
as O
saying O
that O
Abedin B-PERSON
“ O
feels O
a O
deep O
responsibility O
to O
encourage O
more O
mutual O
understanding O
between O
her O
beliefs O
and O
culture O
and O
American B-NORP
culture O
. O
” O

non_propaganda
It O
turns O
out O
that O
some O
of O
the O
e O
- O
mails O
were O
accessed O
by O
foreign O
parties O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
bullet O
that O
pierced O
her O
back O
had O
ricocheted O
off O
the O
concrete O
ground O
after O
it O
was O
fired O
by O
Garcia B-PERSON
Zarate I-PERSON
from O
a O
handgun O
belonging O
to O
a O
federal O
ranger O
that O
had O
been O
stolen O
four B-DATE
days I-DATE
earlier I-DATE
. O

propaganda
Nowhere O
! O

non_propaganda
Kavanaugh O
even O
responded O
by O
pointing O
out O
that O
even O
her O
friends O
said O
they O
do O
n't O
recall O
such O
an O
incident O
and O
had O
literally O
hundreds B-CARDINAL
of O
people O
commend O
his O
character O
as O
the O
direct O
opposite O
of O
what O
Ford B-ORG
claims O
. O

non_propaganda
In O
July B-DATE
2010 I-DATE
, O
the O
ADL B-ORG
condemned O
Zakkout B-GPE
and O
his O
group O
AMANA B-ORG
for O
featuring O
an O
anti B-NORP
- I-NORP
Jewish I-NORP
video O
produced O
by O
former O
KKK B-ORG
leader O
and O
white O
supremacist O
David B-PERSON
Duke I-PERSON
on O
the O
AMANA B-ORG
website O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
formation O
of O
the O
formators O
and O
their O
collaborators O
is O
entrusted O
in O
part O
to O
the O
monasteries O
and O
in O
part O
to O
the O
Federation O
, O
therefore O
, O
the O
President O
of O
the O
Federation B-ORG
is O
called O
to O
strengthen O
formation O
at O
the O
federal O
level O
and O
to O
require O
the O
participation O
of O
those O
who O
exercise O
the O
service O
of O
formation O
; O
if O
this O
does O
not O
happen O
, O
she O
will O
refer O
the O
matter O
to O
the B-ORG
Holy I-ORG
See I-ORG
. O

propaganda
His O
presence O
on O
the O
boards O
of O
both O
organizations O
constitutes O
an O
obscene O
travesty O
. O

non_propaganda
No O
, O
Trump B-PERSON
didn O
’ O
t O
start O
the O
fire O
. O

non_propaganda
Don O
’ O
t O
forget O
, O
after O
all O
, O
that O
that O
’ O
s O
what O
Oswald B-PERSON
said O
. O

non_propaganda
If O
it O
were O
simply O
a O
popularity O
contest O
, O
Bible B-WORK_OF_ART
in O
the O
Schools O
would O
be O
allowed O
to O
continue O
as O
is O
. O

non_propaganda
I O
was O
in O
Africa B-LOC
as O
a O
missionary O
and O
as O
bishop O
for O
30 B-DATE
years I-DATE
. O

non_propaganda
We O
moved O
NATO B-ORG
into O
Eastern B-LOC
Europe I-LOC
and O
the O
Baltic B-NORP
, O
onto O
her O
doorstep O
. O

propaganda
They O
know O
that O
the O
eleven B-CARDINAL
male O
Republican B-NORP
Senators O
on O
the B-ORG
Judiciary I-ORG
Committee I-ORG
dread O
the O
# O
MeToo O
movement O
casting O
them O
as O
knuckle O
- O
dragging O
Neanderthal B-NORP
sexists O
who O
want O
to O
“ O
silence O
” O
the O
accuser O
with O
their O
“ O
cavalier O
treatment O
of O
a O
sexual O
assault O
survivor O
, O
” O
as O
one B-CARDINAL
Ford B-ORG
lawyer O
has O
said O
. O

propaganda
As O
the O
new O
dispensation O
’ O
s O
foremost O
theologian O
, O
St. B-GPE
Paul I-GPE
would O
declare O
, O
the O
old O
penalty O
remained O
very O
much O
in O
force O
: O
“ O
Almost O
all O
things O
, O
according O
to O
the O
law O
, O
are O
cleansed O
with O
blood O
: O
and O
without O
the O
shedding O
of O
blood O
there O
is O
no O
remission O
. O
” O
It O
is O
still O
“ O
appointed O
for O
men O
once O
to O
die O
, O
and O
after O
this O
the O
judgment O
” O
( O
Heb B-PERSON
. O

non_propaganda
Losing O
a O
high O
- O
profile O
fight O
is O
always O
going O
to O
hurt O
a O
president O
, O
which O
is O
why O
they O
should O
take O
care O
to O
avoid O
high O
- O
risk O
, O
low O
- O
reward O
conflicts O
. O

non_propaganda
Over O
a O
12-month O
period O
an O
average O
of O
perhaps O
300,000 B-CARDINAL
immigrants O
die O
and O
an O
equal O
number O
leave O
the O
U.S. B-GPE
voluntarily O
. O

propaganda
As O
I O
understand O
Julian B-PERSON
, O
this O
is O
something O
he O
would O
not O
even O
contemplate O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
most O
famous O
of O
these O
galaxies O
is O
, O
of O
course O
, O
the B-ORG
Andromeda I-ORG
Galaxy I-ORG
, O
which O
gets O
its O
name O
from O
the O
large O
constellation O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
secretary O
got O
a O
call O
from O
White B-ORG
House I-ORG
chief O
of O
staff O
John B-PERSON
Kelly I-PERSON
but O
only O
got O
told O
an O
unspecified O
presidential O
tweet O
concerning O
him O
may O
be O
coming O
, O
officials O
at O
the B-ORG
State I-ORG
Department I-ORG
told O
the O
wire O
service O
. O

non_propaganda
His O
latest O
research O
looks O
at O
how O
search O
engines O
can O
affect O
voters O
by O
suggesting O
negative O
or O
positive O
search O
terms O
when O
a O
political O
candidate O
’ O
s O
name O
is O
entered O
into O
the O
search O
bar O
. O

non_propaganda
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O
_ O

non_propaganda
They O
appealed O
to O
the O
US B-GPE
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
to O
exempt O
them O
from O
sanctions O
as O
they O
continue O
to O
do O
business O
with O
Tehran B-GPE
. O

non_propaganda
The B-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
Times I-ORG
has O
now O
run O
its O
own O
explainer O
piece O
on O
Farrakhan B-GPE
and O
the O
Dems B-NORP
which O
mentions O
the O
infamous O
Obama B-ORG
- I-ORG
Farrakhan I-ORG
photo O
. O

non_propaganda
One B-CARDINAL
hundred I-CARDINAL
thousand I-CARDINAL
persons O
were O
killed O
in O
Fez O
on O
that O
occasion O
, O
and O
120,000 B-CARDINAL
in O
Marrakesh B-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
— O
WHO O
( O
@ O
WHO O
) O
May B-DATE
8 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2018 I-DATE

non_propaganda
San B-GPE
Antonio I-GPE
police O
told O
Fox B-ORG
News I-ORG
on O
Thursday B-DATE
they O
had O
received O
a O
complaint O
and O
detectives O
had O
been O
assigned O
to O
the O
case O
. O

non_propaganda
On O
Feb. B-DATE
17 I-DATE
, O
he O
sent O
a O
senior O
Vatican B-FAC
sex O
abuse O
investigator O
, O
Archbishop B-PERSON
Charles I-PERSON
Scicluna I-PERSON
, O
to O
New B-GPE
York I-GPE
to O
interview O
Cruz B-PERSON
, O
who O
now O
lives O
in O
Philadelphia B-GPE
. O

propaganda
“ O
But O
to O
me O
this O
seems O
a O
pretty O
clear O
violation O
of O
the O
Constitution B-LAW
. O
” O

non_propaganda
In O
a O
letter O
to O
May B-DATE
, O
he O
said O
: O
“ O
I O
am O
writing O
to O
you O
to O
ask O
you O
and O
the O
home O
secretary O
to O
take O
immediate O
action O
to O
ban O
the O
president O
of O
the B-GPE
United I-GPE
States I-GPE
, O
Donald B-PERSON
Trump I-PERSON
, O
from O
entering O
the B-GPE
United I-GPE
Kingdom I-GPE
, O
due O
to O
his O
apparent O
support O
for O
far O
- O
right O
groups O
in O
this O
country O
. O

non_propaganda
They O
were O
due O
to O
attend O
a O
march O
planned O
by O
the O
far O
- O
right O
EDL B-ORG
to O
mark O
Armed B-ORG
Forces I-ORG
Day I-ORG
on O
29 B-DATE
June I-DATE
, O
ending O
in O
Woolwich B-GPE
, O
south B-GPE
east I-GPE
London I-GPE
, O
where O
soldier O
Drummer B-PERSON
Rigby I-PERSON
was O
murdered O
last B-DATE
month I-DATE
. O

propaganda
While O
there O
are O
still O
other O
problems O
as O
well O
, O
such O
as O
gas O
stations O
being O
slow O
to O
reopen O
, O
and O
roads O
getting O
badly O
damaged O
, O
the O
power O
grid O
’ O
s O
utter O
annihilation O
in O
the O
category O
4 B-CARDINAL
winds O
is O
not O
just O
a O
temporary O
inconvenience O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
letter O
bolsters O
TheDCNF O
’ O
s O
previous O
reporting O
about O
the O
missing O
server O
and O
evidence O
of O
fraud O
on O
Capitol B-ORG
Hill I-ORG
. O

propaganda
Democrats B-NORP
are O
pulling O
out O
all O
the O
stops O
and O
enabling O
salacious O
last B-TIME
- I-TIME
minute I-TIME
accusations O
against O
Supreme B-ORG
Court I-ORG
nominee O
Judge O
Brett B-PERSON
Kavanaugh I-PERSON
in O
order O
to O
sink O
his O
candidacy O
. O

non_propaganda
Pilger O
’ O
s O
Statement O

non_propaganda
If O
, O
as O
a O
result O
of O
the O
process O
of O
discernment O
, O
undertaken O
with O
“ O
humility O
, O
discretion O
and O
love O
for O
the O
Church B-ORG
and O
her O
teaching O
, O
in O
a O
sincere O
search O
for O
God O
’ O
s O
will O
and O
a O
desire O
to O
make O
a O
more O
perfect O
response O
to O
it O
” O
( O
AL B-PRODUCT
300 I-PRODUCT
) O
, O
a O
separated O
or O
divorced O
person O
who O
is O
living O
in O
a O
new O
relationship O
manages O
, O
with O
an O
informed O
and O
enlightened O
conscience O
, O
to O
acknowledge O
and O
believe O
that O
he O
or O
she O
are O
at O
peace O
with O
God O
, O
he O
or O
she O
can O
not O
be O
precluded O
from O
participating O
in O
the O
sacraments O
of O
Reconciliation O
and O
the O
Eucharist O
( O
see O
AL B-ORG
, O
notes O
336 B-CARDINAL
and O
351 B-CARDINAL
) O
. O

propaganda
Information O
has O
come O
out O
that O
the B-LAW
Crown I-LAW
Prosecution I-LAW
Service I-LAW
tried O
to O
prevent O
the O
Swedes B-NORP
from O
giving O
up O
the O
case O
against O
Julian B-NORP
on O
bogus O
sexual O
assault O
charges O
. O

non_propaganda
But O
while O
this O
internal O
grumbling O
took O
place O
, O
mainstream O
media O
dutifully O
reported O
official O
statements O
as O
if O
the O
veracity O
of O
the O
information O
couldn O
’ O
t O
be O
disputed O
. O

non_propaganda
Marie B-PERSON
Collins I-PERSON
, O
the O
Irish B-NORP
abuse O
survivor O
and O
Commission O
member O
who O
resigned O
, O
citing O
the O
Vatican B-FAC
’ O
s O
refusal O
to O
take O
meaningful O
action O
, O
told O
AP B-ORG
, O
“ O
When O
we O
gave O
him O
[ O
O O
’ O
Malley B-PERSON
] O
the O
letter O
for O
the O
pope O
, O
he O
assured O
us O
he O
would O
give O
it O
to O
the O
pope O
and O
speak O
of O
the O
concerns O
. O

propaganda
Hungary B-GPE
's O
Prime O
Minister O
Viktor B-PERSON
Orban I-PERSON
has O
been O
somewhat O
of O
a O
lone O
voice O
in O
Europe B-LOC
against O
the O
Muslim B-NORP
invasion O
, O
and O
on O
Wednesday B-DATE
he O
gave O
a O
` O
` O
Hungary O
First O
'' O
speech O
in O
which O
he O
declared O
that O
he O
would O
` O
` O
fight O
those O
who O
want O
to O
change O
the O
Christian O
Identity O
of O
Europe B-LOC
. O
'' O

non_propaganda
Therefore O
he O
that O
resisteth O
the O
power O
, O
resisteth O
the O
ordinance O
of O
God O
, O
and O
they O
that O
resist O
purchase O
to O
themselves O
eternal O
damnation O
. O

non_propaganda
Trump B-PERSON
showed O
Kim B-PERSON
the O
movie O
on O
an O
iPad O
during O
their O
talks O
. O

propaganda
We O
hosted O
an O
event O
with O
over B-CARDINAL
200 I-CARDINAL
people O
and O
a O
hangout O
with O
social O
media O
influencers O
about O
the O
power O
of O
the O
Latino B-PERSON
vote O
and O
the O
new O
research O
Nielsen B-PERSON
published O
about O
the O
Latino B-PERSON
electorate O
. O

non_propaganda
We O
had O
a O
long O
hiatus O
in O
which O
the O
popes O
pretended O
nothing O
essential O
had O
changed O
, O
while O
the O
institution O
around O
them O
fell O
to O
the O
New O
Paradigm O
, O
until O
the O
papacy O
was O
the O
only O
thing O
left O
. O

non_propaganda
Whoever O
greets O
him O
participates O
in O
his O
evil O
works O
. O
” O
( O
2 O
John O
1.10 O
- O
11 O
) O
; O
“ O
If O
anyone O
preaches O
to O
you O
a O
different O
Gospel B-ORG
, O
let O
him O
be O
accursed O
! O
” O
( O
Galatians B-NORP
1.8 B-CARDINAL
- O
9 B-CARDINAL
) O

non_propaganda
Hogan O
was O
a O
Bush B-PERSON
appointee O
who O
respected O
the O
law O
. O

non_propaganda
That O
is O
often O
followed O
by O
vomiting O
and O
diarrhoea O
, O
skin O
eruptions O
, O
kidney O
and O
liver O
failure O
, O
and O
internal O
and O
external O
bleeding O
. O

non_propaganda
That O
’ O
s O
why O
the O
CIA B-ORG
targeted O
Guatemala B-GPE
for O
regime O
change O
and O
why O
it O
targeted O
Arbenz B-ORG
and O
other O
Guatemalan B-PERSON
officials O
for O
assassination O
. O

non_propaganda
Is O
it O
any O
wonder O
that O
priests O
and O
laity O
alike O
are O
changing O
their O
attitude O
on O
the O
` B-WORK_OF_ART
` I-WORK_OF_ART
gay I-WORK_OF_ART
lifestyle I-WORK_OF_ART
'' I-WORK_OF_ART
and O
violations O
of O
the B-LAW
Sixth I-LAW
Commandment I-LAW
when O
so O
many O
bishops O
are O
working O
to O
remove O
the O
stigma O
attached O
to O
this O
sin O
that O
Scripture O
tells O
us O
cries O
to O
heaven O
for O
vengeance O
? O

propaganda
If O
Islam B-ORG
is O
a O
good O
religion O
in O
itself O
, O
as O
you O
seem O
to O
teach O
, O
why O
did O
we O
become O
Catholic B-NORP
? O

non_propaganda
The O
essence O
of O
this O
ultimatum O
would O
be O
that O
if O
by O
the B-DATE
end I-DATE
of I-DATE
June I-DATE
a O
consensus O
is O
not O
reached O
in O
the O
council O
of O
EU B-ORG
heads O
of O
government O
, O
then O
the O
planned O
reforms O
would O
be O
adopted O
with O
a O
qualified O
majority O
vote O
which O
would O
overrule O
dissenters O
. O

non_propaganda
Pope O
Benedict B-PERSON
XVI I-PERSON
has O
warned O
against O
precisely O
the O
kind O
of O
“ O
accommodation O
” O
Faggioli B-PERSON
is O
calling O
for O
, O
writing O
that O
when O
“ O
the O
people O
can O
not O
cope O
” O
with O
God O
, O
they O
“ O
bring O
him O
down O
into O
their O
own O
world O
, O
” O
and O
insist O
that O
“ O
he O
must O
be O
the O
kind O
of O
God O
that O
[ O
they O
need O
] O
. O
” O
In O
other O
words O
, O
“ O
Man O
is O
using O
God O
, O
and O
, O
in O
reality O
, O
even O
if O
it O
is O
not O
outwardly O
discernible O
, O
he O
is O
placing O
himself O
above O
God O
. O
” O
To O
fully O
drive O
the O
point O
home O
, O
Benedict B-ORG
equates O
this O
kind O
of O
worship O
with O
the O
Israelites B-NORP
desert O
worship O
of O
the O
bull O
calf O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
assistance O
Google B-ORG
provided O
to O
the O
Clinton B-PERSON
campaign O
likely O
violated O
election O
laws O
and O
served O
as O
an O
unreported O
in O
- O
kind O
contribution O
. O

non_propaganda
When O
we O
look O
at O
what O
is O
going O
on O
in O
CJH B-ORG
’ O
s O
components O
like O
the O
AJHS B-GPE
, O
the O
elevation O
of O
David B-PERSON
N. I-PERSON
Myers I-PERSON
to O
head O
CJH B-ORG
is O
unsurprising O
. O

non_propaganda
Your O
support O
makes O
our O
work O
possible O
. O

non_propaganda
Eventually O
Deal O
moved O
her O
daughter O
to O
a O
public O
school O
a B-QUANTITY
few I-QUANTITY
miles I-QUANTITY
away O
in O
Virginia B-GPE
where O
there O
is O
no O
Bible B-WORK_OF_ART
class O
. O

non_propaganda
In O
the O
name O
of O
the O
transparency O
so O
hailed O
by O
the O
Pope O
, O
the O
report O
that O
the O
Visitator B-ORG
, O
Argentine B-NORP
bishop O
Alcides B-PERSON
Casaretto I-PERSON
, O
delivered O
more B-DATE
than I-DATE
a I-DATE
year I-DATE
ago I-DATE
only O
and O
directly O
to O
the O
Pope O
, O
must O
be O
made O
public O
. O

non_propaganda
Abid O
’ O
s O
attorney O
, O
Jim B-PERSON
Bacon I-PERSON
, O
used O
the O
life O
insurance O
lawsuit O
to O
force O
Gilani B-PERSON
to O
sit O
for O
a O
sworn O
deposition O
Oct. B-DATE
4 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2017 I-DATE
in O
which O
he O
told O
her O
to O
reveal O
what O
she O
told O
the O
FBI B-ORG
about O
the O
congressional O
criminal O
probe O
and O
tried O
to O
get O
her O
to O
find O
out O
details O
from O
investigators O
. O

non_propaganda
It O
is O
relative O
to O
the O
good O
, O
but O
not O
to O
the O
evil O
. O

non_propaganda
On O
Wednesday B-DATE
, O
the O
car O
crashed O
at O
the O
main O
gate O
of O
Travis B-FAC
Air I-FAC
Force I-FAC
Base I-FAC
. O

propaganda
- O
Bishop O
Thomas B-PERSON
Olmsted I-PERSON
of O
Phoenix B-GPE
, O
Arizona B-GPE
, O
issued O
a O
statement O
affirming O
that O
he O
has O
known O
Viganò B-GPE
for O
39 B-DATE
years I-DATE
, O
has O
“ O
always O
known O
and O
respected O
him O
as O
a O
man O
of O
truthfulness O
, O
faith O
and O
integrity O
” O
and O
that O
his O
testimony O
should O
“ O
be O
taken O
seriously O
by O
all O
… O
” O

non_propaganda
In O
case O
you O
haven O
’ O
t O
been O
reading O
the O
McCarrick B-ORG
headlines O
or O
noticing O
the O
plunging O
mass O
attendance O
and O
collections O
, O
Catholics B-NORP
don O
’ O
t O
trust O
their O
boys O
around O
priests O
and O
are O
furious O
that O
their O
seminarians O
are O
subjected O
to O
unrelenting O
homosexual O
sexual O
harassment O
. O

non_propaganda
It O
has O
no O
value O
at O
all O
. O

non_propaganda
deals O
with O
issues O
of O
major O
importance O
; O
makes O
decisions O
and O
issues O
norms O
that O
all O
nuns O
are O
required O
to O
observe O
, O
after O
the O
definitive O
approval O
of O
the B-ORG
Holy I-ORG
See I-ORG
; O

non_propaganda
And O
I O
am O
building O
a O
seminary O
in O
Switzerland B-GPE
. O

propaganda
“ O
I O
have O
some O
pretty O
severe O
things O
we O
’ O
re O
thinking O
about O
, O
” O
Trump B-PERSON
said O
of O
North B-GPE
Korea I-GPE
at O
a O
news O
conference O
in O
Warsaw B-GPE
. O

non_propaganda
Myers O
is O
a O
symptom O
of O
the O
problem O
. O

non_propaganda
For O
obvious O
reasons O
I O
can O
’ O
t O
identify O
them O
, O
even O
to O
say O
what O
country O
they O
are O
in O
. O

propaganda
RIO B-ORG
DE I-ORG
JANEIRO I-ORG
— O
Brazilian B-NORP
police O
say O
the O
man O
considered O
to O
be O
the O
country O
’ O
s O
largest O
arms O
dealer O
has O
been O
arrested O
in O
the B-GPE
United I-GPE
States I-GPE
by O
Immigration O
and O
Customs O
Enforcement O
agents O
. O

non_propaganda
Pic O
: O
NASA B-ORG

propaganda
CAPITOL O
POLICE O
ACCIDENTALLY O
GAVE O
EVIDENCE O
TO O
HOUSE O
HACKING O
SUSPECT O
’ O
S O
DEFENSE O
ATTORNEY O
By O
Luke B-PERSON
Rosiak I-PERSON
on O
May B-DATE
24 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2018 I-DATE
: O

non_propaganda
Although O
the O
issue O
came O
to O
the O
attention O
of O
a O
much O
broader O
audience O
during O
the O
most O
recent O
papal O
trip O
, O
the O
outcry O
has O
been O
ongoing O
since O
his O
appointment O
to O
the O
southern O
Chilean O
diocese O
of O
Osorno B-ORG
in O
2015 B-DATE
. O

propaganda
God O
help O
us O
. O

propaganda
This O
is O
another O
case O
of O
Kavanaugh B-ORG
Derangement I-ORG
Syndrome I-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
When O
the O
new O
Bishop B-ORG
Mark B-PERSON
Seitz I-PERSON
took O
possession O
of O
the O
Diocese O
of O
El B-GPE
Paso I-GPE
on O
July B-DATE
9 I-DATE
, I-DATE
2013 I-DATE
, O
I O
sent O
the O
first B-ORDINAL
Counsellor O
, O
Monsignor O
Jean O
- O
François O
Lantheaume O
, O
while O
I O
went O
to O
Dallas B-GPE
that O
same B-DATE
day I-DATE
for O
an O
international O
meeting O
on O
Bioethics B-GPE
. O

non_propaganda
In O
court O
documents O
, O
Gilani B-PERSON
alleged O
, O
“ O
while O
he O
was O
admitted O
in O
hospital O
my O
telephone O
conversations O
were O
taped O
and O
some O
other O
recording O
devices O
were O
also O
installed O
/ O
planted O
in O
my O
house O
… O
Imran B-PERSON
Awan I-PERSON
showed O
up O
and O
threatened O
me O
for O
me O
calling O
the O
police O
. O

propaganda
Clearly O
, O
Ford B-ORG
has O
been O
outed O
as O
a O
radical O
political O
activist O
who O
promotes O
baby O
murder O
and O
other O
unlawful O
actions O
. O

non_propaganda
Capitol B-ORG
Police I-ORG
are O
looking O
into O
the O
massive O
amounts O
of O
data O
the O
Awans B-NORP
reportedly O
downloaded O
off O
the O
congressional O
system O
, O
thousands B-CARDINAL
of O
illegal O
logins O
made O
on O
the O
official O
system O
, O
possible O
theft O
of O
tens B-MONEY
of I-MONEY
thousands I-MONEY
of I-MONEY
dollars I-MONEY
in O
congressional O
equipment O
and O
fraud O
and O
sent O
to O
foreign O
governments O
and O
groups O
. O

non_propaganda
Trump B-PRODUCT
is O
right O
. O

non_propaganda
The O
article O
recounted O
a O
claim O
by O
Deborah B-PERSON
Ramirez I-PERSON
, O
a O
Yale B-ORG
classmate O
of O
Brett B-FAC
Kavanaugh I-FAC
’ I-FAC
s I-FAC
, O
concerning O
“ O
a O
dormitory O
party O
gone O
awry O
. O
” O
As O
the O
article O
acknowledged O
, O
however O
, O
“ O
her O
memories O
contained O
gaps O
because O
she O
had O
been O
drinking O
at O
the O
time O
of O
the O
alleged O
incident O
. O
” O
The O
article O
goes O
on O
to O
say O
that O
in O
her O
initial O
conversations O
with O
The B-ORG
New I-ORG
Yorker I-ORG
, O
Ms. O
Ramirez B-PERSON
was O
“ O
reluctant O
to O
characterize O
Kavanaugh O
’ O
s O
role O
in O
the O
alleged O
incident O
with O
certainty O
. O
” O
It O
was O
only O
after O
“ O
six B-DATE
days I-DATE
of O
carefully O
assessing O
her O
memories O
and O
consulting O
with O
her O
attorney O
” O
that O
Ms. O
Ramirez B-PERSON
was O
suddenly O
able O
to O
pinpoint O
Judge O
Kavanaugh B-PERSON
as O
having O
committed O
an O
unsavory O
act O
, O
even O
though O
she O
admitted O
being O
“ O
foggy O
” O
at O
the O
time O
. O

non_propaganda
Possible O
solutions O
: O
we O
are O
making O
enquiries O
. O

propaganda
At O
this B-TIME
moment I-TIME
, O
the O
entire O
Novus B-PERSON
Ordo I-PERSON
regime O
of O
novelty O
is O
threatened O
with O
collapse O
on O
account O
of O
its O
homosexual O
corruption O
, O
and O
voices O
throughout O
the O
Catholic B-NORP
world O
are O
now O
echoing O
Archbishop B-NORP
Viganò O
’ O
s O
call O
for O
Bergoglio B-PERSON
’ O
s O
resignation O
, O
including O
Laura B-PERSON
Ingraham I-PERSON
: O
“ O
Too O
little O
, O
too O
late O
from O
Pope B-PERSON
Francis I-PERSON
in O
Ireland B-GPE
. O

non_propaganda
He O
didn O
’ O
t O
speak O
up O
when O
they O
came O
for O
the O
Jews B-NORP
because O
he O
wasn O
’ O
t O
a O
Jew O
. O

non_propaganda
Scumbag O
shooter O
Stephen B-PERSON
Paddock I-PERSON
LEFT O
A O
NOTE O
, O
see O
new O
pics O
from O
inside O
hotel O
room O
! O

propaganda
Were O
the O
Ammonites O
and O
Moabites O
not O
kept O
out O
of O
the O
assembly O
of O
Israel B-GPE
because O
of O
their O
hatred O
of O
the O
people O
of O
God O
? O

non_propaganda
Bergoglio B-PERSON
Pleads I-PERSON
the O
Fifth B-ORDINAL

non_propaganda
. O

non_propaganda
Haig B-ORG
also O
said O
that O
he O
received O
death O
threats O
after O
his O
name O
was O
revealed O
this B-DATE
week I-DATE
. O

non_propaganda
Subscribe O
Today B-DATE
! O

non_propaganda
The O
Julian O
Assange O
case O
reminds O
me O
of O
the O
Gary B-PERSON
Webb I-PERSON
case O
. O

non_propaganda
Any O
financial O
support O
would O
be O
appreciated O
for O
the O
time O
he O
would O
need O
to O
recover O
. O
” O

non_propaganda
Orban B-ORG
's O
border O
wall O
virtually O
eliminated O
illegal O
immigration O
. O

non_propaganda
P.S O
. O

propaganda
He O
said O
the O
group O
was O
a O
toothless O
, O
paper O
- O
shuffling O
exercise O
. O

non_propaganda
That O
’ O
s O
a O
demonstrably O
true O
statement O
. O

propaganda
Then O
he O
suggests O
that O
healing O
and O
reconciliation O
will O
only O
come O
if O
we O
take O
a O
hard O
look O
at O
our O
own O
flaws O
… O
. O

non_propaganda
Just O
so O
we O
're O
all O
clear O
. O

non_propaganda
In O
his O
letter O
, O
Fr O
. O

propaganda
And O
if O
the O
episcopal O
retort O
is O
going O
to O
be O
that O
this O
acceptance O
refers O
only O
to O
chaste O
homosexuals O
, O
then O
we O
call O
FOUL O
even O
louder O
since O
this O
crosses O
the O
line O
into O
willful O
deception O
. O

propaganda
When O
I O
die O
and O
go O
before O
the O
judge O
, O
God B-PERSON
will O
not O
be O
able O
to O
say O
to O
me O
, O
“ O
You O
destroyed O
the O
Church B-ORG
. O
” O
I O
refused O
to O
contribute O
to O
the O
destruction O
of O
the O
Church B-ORG
. O

non_propaganda
Mariawald B-PERSON
was O
consequently O
affiliated O
, O
in O
the O
manner O
this O
document O
describes O
, O
with O
a O
liberal O
house O
in O
the O
Netherlands B-GPE
whose O
superior O
, O
unsurprisingly O
, O
discovered O
that O
the O
house O
was O
hopelessly O
divided O
and O
could O
not O
be O
saved O
. O
